<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[POC love talking about police brutality but noone talks about black on white crime. Thank you cops for dealing with the thugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White boys need men around them. Jews raise their kids to love money. Whites need to raise kids to love their race,family, &amp; friends. #HASHTAG#/88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're white &amp; a feminist you're no different than a Jew. White women are beautiful, intelligent,perfect stand by the white man not hoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people need to stop fighting other whites. You see blacks &amp; Jews are starting to work together &amp; that killing us. Whites stand United.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White kids need to grow up around other white kids so that Jewish &amp; nigga ideology doesn't affect them. White community's for white people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Never been ashamed to call yourself a white man. I'm proud of my people &amp; will always help them stay woke! 14/88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Black women try so hard to be white! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Unlike Black Americans African boys know their father until he dies from ebola.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 99% of all my family members have AIDS! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate my math teacher but Science is next I love that subject!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# When Jewish people benefit from the hard work of the white man from over century's of abuse. Jews are rich cause of whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White Lives Matter Movement fights Jewish supremacy!Big Banks,Media, Social Changes.Jews want to destroy anything whites have created]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ I love Her! I want a kid so bad! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cute 14/88 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank You ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Officer #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After I'm done with high school maybe I should be a cop. It looks so fun man! I can't wait I'm joining the military then law enforcement!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Failed to comply with cops orders,cops shot him,now he smoking weed with the angels.Thank U Cops ðŸ‘® #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about to head for my next class. Economics! 9 out of 10 the room will be full of Jews lol! Be back in a few! âœŒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I dislike niggers that doesn't mean hate. I just disagree with them being niggers. Same as someone who disagrees about homosexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism is not even real.All races look after their own kind.A personally like my race &amp; culture cause its the best on the planet hands down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will continue&amp;always say proudly I don't like Jews or blacks I'm serious say I'm trolling,fake,or whatever.Point is keep them away from me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of my classmates know my views. I'm not to out there in public yet. So far I'm more open online but I'm starting to speak out more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I like; 1.Hardcore Heavy Mental 2. Fighting 3. Women (white ones) 4.Helping out in my communityðŸ‘· Dislike; 1.Jews 2. Black kids 3.Fags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like other cultures that are not white for real. That not a crime nor is it harming anyone! Pro white doesn't mean anti nigger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My class is having a small break time now. People keep asking me my views. Online &amp; in real life. It simple I just stand for my people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, Fuck,Fuck,Fuck! Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, Fuck,Fuck,Fuck! Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, Fuck, The Jews! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can deal with victory. Only the strong can deal with pain! 14/88 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait till I have kids. I'm homeschooling them!I personally hate being around non whites sometime!So I know they wouldn't like it to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My cousin had her baby 5 days ago. I can't wait to start playing with &amp; teaching this kid everything I know! ðŸ’–ðŸ’—ðŸ’˜ðŸ’ðŸ’ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# It's nothing more than rich Jews brainwashing people into thinking niggerism,homosexuality,anti white hate speech is cool.Fuck them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the past 8 weeks people have been sentencing me death threats. This just proves my point its a war on white men. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School tomorrow I'm lucky I wasn't grouped with those black kids. I have a two week project to do &amp; I don't want niggas to fuck up my grades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm heading to bed! ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´Good Night! Fuck the Jews Fuck the Blacks Fuck the Latinos Fuck the Asians Fuck the Native Americans Love you whitesâœŠ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14/88 "Hate is more lasting than dislike" -Adolf Hitler #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its almost lunch time.My teacher planning on putting us in groups.There are 7 blacks in my class!I hope to god I don't get put with them. ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In history class they're talking about WW2. I hate how teachers lie to students about German history.Stop blaming Hitler &amp; blame the Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Latino&amp;Black history months aren't real. Slaves &amp; Immigrants are nothing more than construction workers for whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so happy there are no Jews going to my school.Its already bad we have black kids going here.So far classes are good but I hate math lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love weapons mostly guns &amp; knives. I'm getting good at using them. å14/88å #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# The purpose of literature is to turn blood into Art." 14/88 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All races need to have their own space so #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# These saying are racist &amp;discriminated against white people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malia Obama is a hypocrite like all black women. She playing the I'm a good role model after she done some bad shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Is a way to shut up people from talking about White Genocide.I stand for whites &amp; whites only! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Hard working black women! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's weird the courthouse is not open for another 15 minutes and I see a line of blacks. Don't they usually show up late?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The illegals took most of the blacks jobs! Fast food, maid service, fruit picking, and janitorial! Don't blame Whitey blame the illegals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Police Brutality the new Welfare system for blacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Counting on you, Trump. To many illegal immigrants walking around here not paying taxes. Its hurting America mainly Whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminists think white men are evil that code for I'm turning gay that will show them or no white man loves me cause I'm ugly(that true).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# A see gay couples adopting white children. The sick things these homosexuals maybe doing to them. Makes my stomach hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# You're a Jew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Preserving, Defending, and Promoting, the White Race is the only hope in creating a better world! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I see an interracial couple! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Brown is just another Michael Brown. A thug that thinks he can break the law&amp; get away with it.Don't drop the soap in jail Chris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police retrieved at least one gun, other weapons and drugs after a raid at Chris Brown's home. Thank you cops!ðŸ‘® #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media is calling Trump Hitler.The same media that called Hitler a monster for making Germany great again.Jewish history always repeats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry Rice vs Angry Black People! 9 out of 10 some how some way they will start blaming white people like they always do. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry Rice said "All lives matter" black people be like; #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Matter #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# For us black people need to stop thinking black is beautiful because its not. This is real beauty. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# for white people. Blacks need to go burn down Jewish businesses.They are the ones who keep you in poverty not whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people can't be racist because whites don't have any power.Jews are the real racists because they control the banks,media,&amp;government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting us against harm! Dogs are true heroes! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I buy 99% of my drugs from the cops. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# about when Jesus said that interracial sex is punishable by being stoned to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Blacks (All of them) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Jews are the original pro blacks. Think about it POC steal so do Jews.POC like money so do Jews.POC hate whites so do Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whites lives are the only lives that matters because you black apes want us dead. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear, #HASHTAG# when you scream blacks lives matter your insulting the white lives matter movement. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people been helping blacks out. Welfare, food stamps, housing programs. Its time for you niggas to get a job. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your home is Africa check the history books. White people don't want blacks  need them in the U.S. so peace! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Jews control the media and want to start a race war to kill off all white people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Pro white doesn't mean racist. Pro white means love for ones culture. ðŸ»ðŸºðŸ¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Always be nice &amp; caring to White Women because they are the Queens of all Womanhood.ðŸ’™ðŸ’šðŸ’› #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ur not racist for thinking Leslie Jones isnt funny, Ur not racist for thinking Leslie Jones isnt attractive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hacked Leslie Jones pics are actually from a National Geographic show! This is better then "Animal Planet". ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hackers must have had 20/20 vision to see a picture of Leslie Jones in the dark. On an owls best day they could not even see her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you search for Leslie Jones nake this pops up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop White People" Whites make up half of all doctors in the U.S. lf you want to stop whites so bad tell her thatðŸ‘‡! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop White People" Before whites &amp; after we stop them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# That we have white only scholarships because every other race beside whites get money for just being their race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Having Jewish Blood #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Give a man a nation &amp; watch him become a God. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# White girls are beautiful angels. ðŸ˜‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# White culture for white people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because this is what happens when you let other races raise white kids. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because studies have shown race mixing can causes deformed baby's. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter People that have a problem with the confederate flag but say nothing about Black power flags are just hypocrites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because before immigrants &amp; liberals this was America ðŸ˜Š #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter White people have been discriminated against for century's.Slavery was trade,Jim Crow was equality,facts are facts. ðŸ‘ŠðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people say #HASHTAG# that discriminating against White Lives Matter Movement. Whites are dying &amp; people think its a joke. Sick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because whites have to live in fear everyday thanks to evil like this; #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter vs Black Lives Matter #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No! Read my posts 100% National Socialist! 1488 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because when a white woman gets rape for 400 years of slavery noone protests yet a thug gets shot white community's burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because we are sick of the Obama administration &amp; liberals pushing homosexuality onto kids! ðŸ‘ŽðŸ’€ðŸ’€ðŸ’€ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because the White Family is the heart of this country&amp;this 76 Genders Homo agenda is killing us. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter Because when thugs like Michael Brown&amp;hate groups like #HASHTAG# can attack whites people need to know we matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter doesn't mean all other lives doesn't matter but right now whites are being killed off by the Jews&amp;Niggas. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Lives Matter The world is trying to kill off these beautiful queens we need people to know their life matters. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The schools &amp; universities are all controlled by Jews. I don't believe one word a liberal teacher says. I research things myself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to Robert Jay Mathews? I haven't seen him around at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out with friends (whites only) ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm back been busy with school &amp; my GF. So far my world gone to hell my teacher is a Jew! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Things black kids do not say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# he must be 50 or locked up like must black men! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No no hood rats, thugs, &amp; Jews just need to learn their place from time to time! ðŸ˜‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting you're 30 but your hair says made in China &amp; good black don't crack unless a cop does it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When they try to be white but remember they skin is black as night! ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell that to the Maury show. A black woman has no limits when it comes down to having kids out of wedlock. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You look like one of the monsters from Ghostbusters! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that a bad thing. Without black males crime rates would go down. Simple fact black women stop having kids! ðŸ˜‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ’‡ðŸ’… Future pornstars in the making! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grow some real hair &amp; that doesn't mean go buy some horse hair. #HASHTAG# âœŠ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ???? Is your name black No!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The issue was a race thing as you people make it to be. Second I didn't say u boy I know its hard but try reading. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thugs kill 30 cops Thugs shot at cops Thugs die End of story #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't do it! Dude innocent! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares! Blacks make a mistake all the time when they kill people in their community. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grow up! You blacks kill people all the time now its a big deal that a cop does it. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good! The police did a great job! Life goes on! And another thug is dead! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# A world without the Jews! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLM is a shill group,made by elitist Jews and these morons have eaten it up. The Jews propaganda is changing its ways to control people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are whites &amp; Italians shooting up people in Chicago hell no its blacks &amp; its blacks nature to commit crimes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White crime is not the topic nor the problem you blacks are! Stats &amp; common sense shows blacks commit more crimes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people make up 13% of the population &amp; commit half of the crimes. What not to get blacks are the problem! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But say nothing about the thousand's of black criminals killing each other. #HASHTAG# is full of shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullshit! When you point a gun at a cop you will get shot. That common sense &amp; black thugs lives don't matter. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# WHITE PRIDE WORLD WIDE! ALL HAIL METAXAS!!! THE GREAT NATIONALIST DICTATOR OF GREECE 80 YEARS EXACTLY AGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you call a black Jew? Answer: HoodRat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# she killed herself by cop because she was crazy how is that an opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# lol views these are facts loser!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm anti black ,anti Jew, anti gay &amp; any other thing that hurts the white race. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good bitch now go kill yourself! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I give a fuck what your saying No! ðŸ˜Š #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it again #HASHTAG# wanted to die. One last welfare queen in the world! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to stop black on black crime 100% is for blacks to leave the country. "ALL" problems solved then. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut yo dumb ass up! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people are angry &amp; most likely to harm or kill someone faster. Read the book Don't Make The Black Kids Angry. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people have common sense &amp; know not to fight with the police. Its not rocket science! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the black on black crime running around these city's &amp; you idiots really think the cops are the problem. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next generation of white people can see how caveman blacks act in society. Hopefully BLMblacks will go away. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you dumb? Answer: Yes! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She had it coming! Let this be a message don't fuck with the police. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone pulls a gun on the cops they will be shot! Besides crazy black women &amp; thugs noone else would do that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people can say whatever we want freedom of speech idiot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slavery, War,Poverty,Jobless, all gets blamed on the white man &amp; people want us to feel guilty about it.No way I say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more the merrier #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it a joke!? Fuck #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# only to me and that will never change ðŸ™…! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you ready to suck my white dick? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All blacks lives matter in jail! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Woman vs The Dark Knight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# She was a bad mother, worst parent, &amp; got what was coming to her. Hopefully all #HASHTAG# people will be this dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Well. The next Rosa Parks she ain't. Shit, the next Michael Brown she ain't. Mother of the year award is a no go too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is full of gays &amp; lesbians. This organization will spread Aids faster then the black women in Africa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American negro is being controlled by Jews using the media. Jews know using people with low intelligence will help kill off whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is running wild in some parts of Europe.If Hitler was still around.Just like the Jews put them into the gas chambers too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware of Jews! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# So black history month is in August now and not February. OK then ðŸ’€ðŸ’€ðŸ’€ðŸ’€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That because blacks are to lazy to go get a job,commit crimes within their community's, &amp; don't have an education. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noone force's black men to commit crimes they just do it. You have only yourself to blame not a system. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homosexuality an abomination so God plan for you is hell! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Can snakes talk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If black people were 4% of the population they still would commit half of the crimes. That what happens when Jews control the media. War!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the one with the problem. White don't even talk about white people this much. You hate being black that all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone mad! Does the truth hurt that black people make up 50% of the crime in the country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black women hate themselves. I believe when you see the word white it makes you feel shamed because you're not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When isn't someone talking about black people you never shut up. You're black we get it now get a life &amp; some hair. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black women raise their children like Michael Brown to fight the cops &amp; break into stores. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any black male between the age of 16-30 will be in jail for committing a crime mostly for selling drugsmurder. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black women raise black kids to be thugs and not follow the law. Then blame the police for their bad parenting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming for someone named jillnothill. Look dumbass if you can't prove me wrong go cry somewhere else. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong! And that doesn't change the fact black women leave their husband's to get on it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# This day is something black people can be proud of. Add black history month and black people should be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people love talking about whites because really they want to be us. They hate themselves so they talk about whites to feel better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noone wants to celebrate black on black crime. Blacks are more dumb,hateful ,and hate themselves a lot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black men don't like black women because you remind them of their mothers. Black mothers give up men for welfare. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black males commit half of the homicides in the country &amp; they are just 13% of the population. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help gays deal with their Aids &amp; low self esteem problems because they have no fathers. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The black kids angry again ðŸ‘‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Rabbi asserts, Islamization of Europe is Good for Jews #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The #HASHTAG# takes you on a one way trip to #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leslie Jones! Funny I didn't see any of your feminist friends back you up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need nationalist super hero's! The Jews run the media so cartoons for kids these days are just brainwashing tools for liberals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Better a poor person who walks in integrity than one crooked in speech and a fool. ~Prov 19:1 #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're dumb ass shit! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# "Little Darkie a niggers tale" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Alice in Church's Chicken #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# black men can't swim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Boyz in the Cotton Fields #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Planet of the Apes! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Yet you're a white guy who supports BLM! You do know they hate white people right! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Wow! Feel better! Twitter is not real life dumbass I don't force my views onto people unlike BLM! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be like a jew and jump into a gas chamber. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigger you just mad people see your BLM group is full of bullshit. If you niggers don't like America leave it shit! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His fat ass and his dad are one of the main reasons people are killing cops! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And how do you know they are not? Playing the shit off like BLM is not a hate group makes you dumb ass shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because it is! You niggers hate whites and police just because you animals have a bad life. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is the sole earthly judge of right and wrong. Hitler Germany will always be in the heart of its people. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>