<author lang="en" class="0">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mississippi Governor Bans Transgenders From Participating In Female Sports #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIBERAL LUNACY: Ice Cream Flavor Name Changed Due to ‘Racism’ Accusations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOC, Nadler Call on N.Y. Gov. Andrew Cuomo to Resign #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Mark Levin goes NUCLEAR on Joe Biden for trying to take credit for Trump's vaccines #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Legislature Just Took 'First Step' Toward Impeaching Cuomo via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transfixed by Trans Fiction #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Lindell's New Free Speech Platform #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Al Goodwyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Are They More Important Than Us?': What the Immigration Crisis Looks Like from a Bar at the Border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING UPDATE: ANTIFA Terrorists Attack Portland Federal Courthouse After Barrier Wall Removed #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive: Biden's Pentagon Chief Overrode National Guard General on Keeping Troops in D.C. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Jack Maxey On Hunter Biden Case: 'Largest National Security Scandal On The Planet' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Rand Paul Reintroduces SCHOOL Act That Gives Parents School Choice #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden: 'We Just Need $2 Trillion In Spending To Flatten The Curve' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: 25% of Republicans That Voted Against Gun Rights Today Also Voted for Trump's Impeachment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mississippi Bans Transgender Athletes From Competing on Girls or Women's Sports Teams #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Signs Executive Order to Make Transgender Surgery Free for Military on Taxpayer Dime #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Tom Stiglich #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Pat Cross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10,000th Victim Comes Forward To Accuse Cuomo Of Inappropriately Killing Her Grandma #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Emperor Is Naked and Senile Too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Patriots Dump Harry And Meghan Into Boston Harbor #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal Obediently Awaits CDC Instructions On Whether It's OK For Him To Breathe #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC Recommends Double-Caging Children At Border For Extra Safety #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Fauci Can't Explain the "Science" For Denying Vaccinated Americans a Return to Travel (VIDEO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump Says He Won't "Support RINOs and Fools," RNC, NRSC, NRCC Back Down #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LA Teachers Told Not To Share Vacation Photos As Unions REFUSE To Return To Classrooms #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creepy Pig Brian Stelter Airs Video of Himself on Live TV Without Pants On (VIDEO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heroic Secret Service Agent Dives In Front Of Biden As Reporter Tries To Ask A Question #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden's Video Editor Pieces Together 2 Minutes Of Coherent Remarks From 2 Hours Of Raw Footage #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Al Goodwyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Pat Cross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronna 'Romney' McDaniel Refuses to Stop Using His Name to Pilfer Money for RINO Republicans #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13-Year-Old Muslim Student Admits She Made Up Story That Led to French Teacher's Beheading #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Sides With Christian Student in College Free Speech Case via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Left Hates Cuomo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Gates, Others Advised Premier Communist Party Propaganda Groups on How to Influence America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Attorney General Makes MASSIVE Announcement Taking Action Against Biden Admin #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Tom Stiglich #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judicial Watch Wants to Know More About Pelosi's Coup Attempt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Glad He's American So He Doesn't Have To Pretend To Care About Royal Family #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's All Folks: Here Are 10 More Looney Tunes Characters That Must Be Canceled #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialists swept Nevada Democrat Party elections. Hours later, the entire staff quit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Issues Damning Statement to All RINOs, Offers New Solution #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOOM: Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene Slams Democrat 'Equality Act'... 'Completely Destroyed Women's Rights' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psaki Confirms That Joe Biden Wants Biological Males to Dominate Women's Sports (VIDEO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Long Day Of Burning Books, Progressive Unwinds By Calling People Nazis #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump Promises to Travel to Alaska and Campaign Against Dead Weight RINO Lisa Murkowski #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brave Browser Planning New Censorship-Free Search Engine Free From Big Tech - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Biden Executive Order Gives Criminals In Jail Increased Voting and Voter Registration Access #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri Republican Senator Roy Blunt Will Not Seek Reelection #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rush Limbaugh's Death Certificate Boasts His G.O.A.T. Status in Epic Fashion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Tom Stiglich #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Approves Release of $3 Billion of Iran's Funds in Iraq, Oman, South Korea #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona Hospital Worker Says Nearly All of New COVID Cases are Illegal Aliens #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This GOP Senator Is Sticking Up for Cheney and Murkowski #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Vows Campaign Against 'Disloyal and Very Bad Senator”... But What Do Polls Suggest? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth Cuomo Accuser: His Actions Caused a Downward Spiral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: Trump Sent a Cease-and-Desist to the RNC Demanding They Stop Using His Name #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mara Elvira Salazar is No Friend of America First Nationalism - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2A Revolution: The Number of Concealed Carry Licenses Issued in Ohio Almost Doubled In 2020 - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican State Rep. From Texas Introduces Bill To Finish Trump Border Wall #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Biden Violated His ‘Oath of Office’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess Who Will be Fundraising for Liz Cheney? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING EXCLUSIVE Coming Out of Georgia... STAY TUNED #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebay Pulls 'Mein Kampf' Upon Discovery Hitler Doodled Chinese Man With Chopsticks In Margins #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progressive Surprised To Learn He Can Still Wear Mask Even Without Government Forcing Him To #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri House Backs Concealed Carry On Public Transportation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barrack Obama Said Pete Buttigieg Was Too Short and Gay to Be President, According to New Book #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic School Students Expelled for Using 'Racist' Acne Medication, Sue for $20 Million #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["End the Border Nightmare" - Trump Slams Joe Biden on Border Crisis in Scathing Statement #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New Dr. Seuss Book, Cat In The Hat Gives Kids Puberty Blockers While Their Mother Isn’t Home #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[600-Page Stimulus Bill To Be Disguised As Nudie Mag To Trick Senators Into Reading It #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Michael Ramirez #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona House Passes Law to Nullify Biden's Federal Gun Control - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco Camera Crew Robbed at Gunpoint While Covering Auto Thefts at Twin Peaks (VIDEO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurrection! Democrats Are Now Trying to Steal Iowa Republican's House Seat #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashli Babbitt's Legal Team Releases First Official Press Release #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay BANS Six Dr. Seuss Books That Will No Longer Be Published Due to "Racist Images" - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROGER STONE EXCLUSIVE: Does CNN Ever Report the Truth? CPAC Rap Video Mischaracterized in Smear #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minnesota Gun Permits Soar To Record Highs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Pat Cross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell your legislatures to adopt this Tennessee bill that makes blocking a highway a felony offense #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Mississippi House, Senate Pass Bill Banning Biological Males from Female Sports #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Deletes All Copies of President Trump's CPAC Speech, Suspends RSBN for Two Weeks #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Moore: White Texans Don't Deserve COVID-19 Vaccine - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As Uselesss as Joe Biden" - EPIC! Marjorie Taylor Greene Sports a New Face Mask on House Floor #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Announces All Bombs Used In The Middle East Will Be Purchased From Black-Owned Businesses #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Passes Sweeping Bill Making it Easier For Democrats to Steal Elections #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Orders Election Do-Over after 78% of Mail-in Ballots Proved Fraudulent -- Notary Arrested #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunter Biden Investigation Active Without Interference From the 'Big Guy's' Administration #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Anthony Fauci: I Do Not Think We’ll Be Back to Normal by March 2022 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attack on Women's Sports Continues As NFL Team Ditches Cheerleaders for Gender Inclusive Dancers #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Weighing 2024 Run Without Pence #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Tom Stiglich #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Lisa Benson #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Michael Ramirez #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POLITICAL HIT? Pro-Trump Portland, Oregon Print Shop Owner Gunned Down in Parking Lot - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One US Contractor Dies After at Least 10 Rockets Hit Air Base Housing US Troops in Iraq: Pentagon #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Administration Cutting COVID-Infected Illegal Immigrants Loose Into Several States - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden FBI Director Christopher Wray Refuses to Disclose Cause of Death for Capitol Officer Sicknick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Al Goodwyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio Concealed Carry Licenses Nearly Doubled In 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nursing Home Was Caught 'Dumping' Residents to Profit Off COVID Patients #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Removes Mask Mandate To Scare All The Californians Away #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuomo Tries To Divert Attention From Sex Scandal By Reminding Everyone Of Nursing Home Scandal #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUV Carrying 27 People Crashes with Semi Truck Near Mexican Border, At Least 15 Killed - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Governor Greg Abbott Ends Statewide Mask Mandate: "It's Time to Open Texas 100%" - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Democrats Disappointed in Sen. Gillibrand's 'Silence' on Gov. Cuomo Allegations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Time to Organize Was Yesterday - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump's 2021 State of the Union Address #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We Don't Like Cuomo Now,' Says Every Late-Night Host In Perfect Robotic Unison #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Cortes: 'Who's Ready For A 2024 Three-Peat' #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa Bill Would Allow Iowans To Purchase, Carry Guns Without A Permit #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden To Give First Address To Congress After He Wakes Up In The Spring #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHOA! More Than 31 Million Viewers Watched Trump’s Speech #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump ‘will be on the ballot in 2024’: Peter Navarro | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll Never Guess Who the New DHS Secretary is Blaming For the Current Border Crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Navarro 'guarantees' at least 3 more indictments coming from Durham special counsel probe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We Love You' Chant Breaks Out During Trump's CPAC Speech! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humiliated Democrats Want to Launch an 'Investigation' Into Ron DeSantis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Offer Compromise That Unborn Babies Are Three-Fifths Of A Person #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford University Babies Demand "Removal" of College Republicans from Campus - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump on The Republican Party: 'It's Becoming the Party of Love' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Trump Aide Planning Run For U.S. House #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Economic Forum Deletes Tweet Claiming ‘Lockdowns’ are ‘Improving Cities’ - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trap? How Cuomo's Sexual Harassment Scandal Helps the Democrats #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Bars and Restaurants Win Court Victory Against Cuomo's COVID Curfew #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Pat Cross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuomo Assures Public He Always Kept Mask On While Sexually Harassing Women #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They Have Betrayed the Constitution - Overwhelming Evidence of FBI Corruption #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At CPAC, Gov. Noem Pushes Back at Dr. Fauci for His Dire Warnings About South Dakota #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Trump Says He May Just Have to Beat Democrats 'a Third Time' -- DEMOCRATS GO NUTS! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No State of the Union Address, No President? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Schools Cancel Advanced Classes Because Being Intelligent and Working Hard is Racist #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: 'Gun Girl' Kaitlin Bennett Confronts CNN's Jim Acosta at CPAC... AGAIN #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Rules That Miss USA Has First Amendment Right to Only Accept Biological Female Contestants #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill would allow individuals to sue government agencies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivy League University Offers Rock Climbing Class — No White Students Allowed #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Expected to Shoot Down Discussion of Starting His Own Party During CPAC Speech #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Kennedy: Trump Got Over 80 Million Votes #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Election #HASHTAG# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Strikes in Syria—None in Cuba #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Vile: Dems Vote Down an Amendment to Aid Students with Mental Health Needs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 100,000 Americans Have Died From COVID-19 on Joe Biden's Watch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by Pat Cross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons - 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Statement from Gen. Michael Flynn Urges Patriots to Fight for Election Integrity - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump GOP Rep. Kinzinger In Trouble In Illinois #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Process Has Begun"- Newsom Recall Movement Organizer Predicts Recall Vote This Fall #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School System 'Cancels' Dr. Seuss Claiming Racial 'Undertones' in Books #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Of Democrat Party Strangely Silent On Andrew Cuomo Sexual Harassment Scandal #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Biden Revokes Trump's Executive Order on Classical Architecture - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Meadows: Trump is 'Planning Next Administration' (VIDEO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rush Limbaugh Laid to Rest in St. Louis #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Patrol Expects 13,000 Illegal Alien Minors to Arrive at the Border in May ALONE - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libs Call for Investigating Justice Thomas' Wife After He Dissents in PA Election Case via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge: Maricopa County Must Provide Ballots From 2020 Election For Audit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep MTG Writes 'THERE ARE ONLY TWO GENDERS' In Skies Above Capitol #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A short primer on the importance of our Second Amendment rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What is Expected During Trump's First Speech Since Leaving the White House #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tommy we are all your Angels We have only one color.Thanks to God ... YOU KEEP HAVING GOOD DAYS....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2024 is Trump’s for the taking #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud Obama Awards His Nobel Peace Prize To Biden For Bombing Syria #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Al-Qaeda Leader Swears Group Is 'As Deadly As When Bin-Laden Lead It' With Biden Now In Office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Hampshire Senate Could Be GOP Pick-Up In 2022: Poll #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Gave Biden Officials Anal COVID Swab Tests "In Error" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Track star sues to stop transgender athletes competing in girls sports | #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHILD ABUSE: Wenatchee High School Forces Kids in Band to Play in Bubbles - Parents Do Nothing #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mail-in ballots and voting machines banned in France #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri County Says It Will Arrest Feds Enforcing Gun Control #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Happened to Joe Biden's State of the Union Address? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If College Basketball Players Don’t Want to Stand for National Anthem, Yank Their Scholarships #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political Cartoons by AF Branco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of Democrats Are Worried About Biden Having Singular Authority to Order Use of Nuclear Weapons #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Will American Jews Wake Up? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers Unions Say Schools Cannot Reopen Until We Are Safe From Our Kids Ever Having A Future #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Sidney Powell's Plan To Primary Out RINOS #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee GOP Calls On Public Universities To Prohibit Athletes From Kneeling During Anthem #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama: "White Resistance" Prevented Reparations Payments to Blacks #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Tech is Now Censoring Content for Amplifying ‘Narratives That Undermine Faith in NATO’ - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Staffer Accuses Gov. Andrew Cuomo of Sexual Harassment #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy Vet Wadi Yakhour Looking to Primary Trump Impeachment Voter Rep. Jaime Herrera Beutler - Big League Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Becoming Senate Budget Committee Chair, Bernie Sanders Quickly Googles 'What Is A Budget' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Did Millions of Dollars in Donations to Black Lives Matter Go? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney Eats Crow; Says Trump Would Win 2024 GOP Nomination In "Landslide" #URL# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>