<author lang="en" class="0">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Congress That’s ‘Shrunk’, Not G-23. What Should Gandhis Do? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A clown can never be taken seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, it must be banned. Both Saif &amp; Producer must be arrested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The scam Master &amp; biggest shadow criminal of Bihar talking of crime-Most funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biggest Joke of Century. He is only free coz of his nuisance value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at their these disguised farmers. Do they look like poor &amp;marginal farmers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hope he also participate in Jailkattu😀Will be great fun for audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hope he also participate in Jailkattu😀Will be great fun for audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This Joker Surjewala is more worried abt his loosing control over HRY farmers &amp; Mandis,thru which they rule like Jagirdars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pranab Da was a true &amp; sensible CONG Leader &amp; deserve all the respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Best example of Farmer on Paper. Badals,Surjewala's etc r more more worried abt their fortunes than genuine farmer's interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heartiest congratulations to Ambani family for new arrival in their family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U r absolutely right Sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do u know the meaning of Democracy or just raising rhetoric. Indian politics will be cleansed once u leave CONG &amp; India]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fittest PM Candidate once Modi Ji voulanteerily retires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do u have self respect after getting dictated by SG? Introspect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, U deserve to be fearful of Indian laws, which ur family have scant respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SS &amp; Leadership of Udhav Thackrey have failed Maharashtra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# RG should have said, absence of a best Remote controlled PM😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, entire Bharat stand behind her to expose SS Goondas &amp;Bollywood drug Mafia, their nexus with underworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answer to Did the Statue of Unity in India fail? by Ashish Shete (आशिष शेटे) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ask Udhav to do a reality check on his Son before making such stupid statements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A very landmark decision, long awaited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope our PM &amp; State CMs watch this video &amp; take immediate action to reduce impact of Pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Blatant lie. It was just a farce show. If someone want to help poor, there is no need of theatrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One feel like to laugh at such rhetoric. Truth.. SG&amp; Vadra Family. Biggest Joke on Earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U &amp; Ur Mother hobnobbed with them.Ask ur Masters ?They may be getting tacit support ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fantastic &amp;apt analogy 😎😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Run fast all three of u,nahi tau Itlay ke buss chuut jayege😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# India should themselves decide abt the survival of this buffoon, looking to people who follow him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In which category u fall😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Show us the proof of cheque issued by Delhi Govt to Railways. India very keen to expose ur lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very true, the left side indeed is deadly virus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If u can't appreciate Govt efforts in fighting the Pandemic, at least don't spread lies&amp;canards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even in such hour of National Crisis,ur immature mind talk of divisive politics-Hall mark of CONG &amp; ur family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most biased &amp; destructive journalist &amp; anti National ,India have ever come across]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes Indeed. Very constructive step. But a word of caution,these Agencies must do due diligence properly before disbursement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Comedy eagerly awaited, but phiss....😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have u in ur life time appreciated any good effort of Govt,except ur own family?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank God,this Lady came out with some sensible statement for the first time in last 20 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, these rioters must be punished severely &amp; must not be released from Jail at any cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All what India can say that this man has lost his mental balance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Stuck in obscure Bangkok Villa😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Best response to most absurd statement of CONG since Independance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very pious thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# India need such MPs &amp; not Netas who merely provide lip service for public cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This scounderal must be traced &amp; jailed for putting entire Country to big risk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes RG&amp;SG should both sit with these Markaz Mullahs&amp;give them some sense. Now where both mother/Son duo hiding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India yet to see any Muslim outfit doing community service,but they r biggest violators of law&amp;crime in India]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indian Muslims must thank their Allah,that they don't get such treatment in India. But they still abuse the establishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What else this community can do?They always flout rules. Arrest all those who don't care for public &amp; put them in Jail for 5 Yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both of u r wealthy.Contribute just 5%of ur last Yr earning for COVID-19 Relief Fund to meet victims expenses &amp; poor food items]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thats what Mullahs r teaching innocent good Indian Muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does such scrupulous sicklurs understand there is lot of difference between faith/Religion &amp; Laws of Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, KPs must teach them lesson for their atrocities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Opportunistic. Pl don't go for excessive appeasement.U have deliberately chosen WB,may be next Kerala for obivious reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such thankless Rogues need to be kicked out of India,who r pursuing their Jehadi Agenda #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And who r these students,mostly muslims or those abetted by foreign media to discredit India]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# India fully endorse the Minister's call. High time these rioters r punished severally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biggest Joke of Century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do India know abt credentials of this SS man ? First find out &amp; then decide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh Mister,if u don't like Indian Institution,gather ur stuff &amp; get deported to a Muslim Country of ur choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sir,corruption at lower levels not rooted out. No accountability of Ministers/Babus towards paid services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# U just wait for ur turn.U guys have looted India left&amp;right. Why r u afraid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# High time this foul mouth Lady must be taught a lesson for her Anti National utterances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC: BBC to stop addressing J&amp;K as India Occupied Kashmir - Sign the Petition! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mamta must stop her useless Rants &amp; focus in development of State&amp; stopping illegal migrants to cross over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cheap men shall always talk cheap things. No political maturity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Congrats to Vihari. Don't let ur guard go down in future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why don't u show big heart. Donate something from ur personal wealth &amp; CONG fund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, what an excuse for rendering a helping hand to ur constituency. As usual dramabazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This man is nuts,rather buffoon, calling Sanskrit a dead language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A big Joke. A man who has resigned long back still acting like owner of a Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Virat&amp;team.India wish all of U best of luck.Make India feel proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indian share Market in doldrums.Govt must withdraw or reduce LTCG both for domestic&amp;FFIs&amp;Dividend Tax for Corporate to boost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Donate at least 0.1% of ur personal wealth.Mere lip service won't work,which dynasty have been doing since last 70 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What if a Muslim outfit does similar things? Can give several examples]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do this buffoon has a mind of its own.Working at behest of dynasty who is out to destroy peace of Nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If any Indian disrespect National Anthem, National song or National Flag, Min 5 Yrs Jail. Cancel Passport of repeat offender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, Mother blessings never go waste, since our Modi Ji from heart respect his mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If such power hungry Netas r permitted to be elected,then public can easily predict their future. Slams these illiterate goons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what the King of treacherous Dynasty has done to India to satisfy his ego against the wishes of all the then CONG leaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article 370 &amp; 35A : History, Origin and Provisions #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# CONG paid Agent, mental Joker.Does he know how international matters r handled. PM must ignore such bufoons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All these things r happening coz of people like u, so keep ur morality &amp; questioning on silent mode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All these cowardly act r happening coz of blunders of CONG &amp; Dynasty initial decisions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Flush out these Rogues&amp;kill them on spot. This is what they deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# RG using the shoulder of his sister in Amethi, where he knows that he has lost his ground against Smiriti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another Dynasty member join the band wagon. When Vadra &amp; his mother will join the fray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# India love your aggression.Just relax fully &amp;rest fully. Recharge ur batteries to ensure victory against NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# BJP should have expelled this loud mouth long time back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Taken a good step to leave the most corrupt Party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Give opportunity to young blood like Prithvi Shaw etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why Govt Agencies are going slow in cases filed against Gandhis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Antony gives such statement to safeguard his future,coz if by mistake CONG comes back to power, Mai will throw him just like a bug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mr Shah has pointed out correct thing for dynasty rhetoric abt Rafale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just eliminate these scoundrels,who thrive on Rest of India money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do the same Voters have a right to ask about health of most powerful force in CONG-Madam Sonia Gandhi. Why double standards?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In fact all WB businessmen must support BJP in their endevour if they want to get rid of TMC goons&amp; increase their businesses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# India think seriously. PM is making a very valid statements. Dynasty must answer this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A pertinent question,which dynasty must answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True. Rogue CONG,particularly the Dynasty have been very soft on terror]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good, all bogus Voters created by AAP removed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is paying for his loyalty to 10,Janpath. He has hurt emotions of 100 Crs Hindus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So whats wrong with that? Is it crime to promote home grown businesses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U will be doing a biggest mistake of ur life in siding with corrupt CONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Again dirty politics. What u were doing in 65 years ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wish u our great Cricketer of the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Muslim appeasement se man bhar gaya, tau Mandir yaad aa gaye. Dirty brand of Politics this dynasty follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Communists ideology have always worked against Hindu faith. CM is playing with fire to play with faith of Hindus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Preaching is very easy than practice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Salute to such good smartens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All stage managed to get sympathy vote. Political gimmicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This brat must be controlled by CONGI leadership,if there is any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sometime pl use ur own mind. Always conveying what 10,Janpath ask u to do so.Height of slavery mindset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not being captured, but cleansed from CONG chamchas, who were installed to serve only interests of dynasty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Again baseless promises, opening up Pandora box. Very amateurish statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These power Hungary lumpen must be forced to apologize to a Senior Bureaucrat,or else must be jailed for misadventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like this man for his frank opinions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just a gimmick for cheap publicity. Nothing beyond that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Amit Shah Ji is absolutely right. Let us give our most courageous PM one more chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very funny,as if these Babus will not ask to grease their palms while visiting homes for fulfillment of work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Absolutely right step. These bank in their individual capacity r big drain on Public money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biggest turncoat of Century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# CONG Ploy. Such people must be ignored. Media have given undesirable coverage to him. Just ignore this goon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# May be he gets some wisdom &amp; start playing constructive opposition role than destructive divisive politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is called height of Slavery mindset of CONGI Pygmy Netas. They never miss chance to butter 10,Janpath Dynasty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Little amazed to see BDutt being emotive on massacre of our brave soldier by her favorite PAK sponsored terror outfits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Again spreading false propaganda to create a wedge among BJP cadre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark Chocolate - Is It Bad For Your Health? via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All public places must be banned for offering prayers in open by any community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has Mr Surjewala ever spoken from his own heart. Seems he carry all instructions from 10,Janpath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A very bad precedent set by this arrogant lady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He has proved himself better suited as a Cheer leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Any sensible person will run away from this man with no substance, only rhetoric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Will somebody ask him from where did he get huge collection of Antique Jewellary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is totally wrong &amp; influenced by wrong forces to give such baseless statements to garner publicity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Then from where they get 9-10 children from each wife ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Look like, a Lowly rated Baccha crying for high marks obtained by another classmate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very bold initiative.Such women must be empowered more&amp; Centre/State must extend all moral &amp; financial help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But actually in above Pic,he definitely look like a Shikanji seller?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If his utterances r collated,a fantastic comedy serial/film could be made.May even win best comedy award]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This guy is fully entrenched &amp; neck deep in corruption cases. Still he is lecturing on Economics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And what u r.A stooge for bargain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Disgruntled person making undesirable noise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is our greatness, that India embraces even scoundrels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SHAME THESE MULLAHS who r doing such heinous crimes of conversion. All Govt aids be with drawn from such Muslim clerics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seems to be true as he is entertaining public thru his childish &amp; immature jibes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# PUT THIS CORRUPT MAN IN JAIL IMMEDIATELY SO THAT PUBLIC DON'T LOOSE FAITH IN OUR JUDICIARY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whole of India is seriously thinking to make a documentary on this great man to make their kids laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Absolute naked truth. Sidda spineless &amp; corrupt Govt must go, if people of Karnataka lounging for better life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Which sensible Judge/Govt official who love his Country will let this buffoon Scot free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# His entry to India must be banned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seems to be Muslim from looks. Who else can dare to do such acts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Doubt whether he ever went to any College for higher studies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These third class lawyers like Bhushan,Sibal etc will even fight for Terrorists to improve their visibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Derek should check hoarding of currency from his boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest contribution of KEJI in Delhi.Majority of Delhites feel, his biggest contribution- Made Delhi 2nd largest slum city in India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indians feel extremely proud of Srikidambi achievement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Congrats Saina &amp; Sindhu. Every Indian feel proud of you. Keep the tri color flying high at all Sports events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Decent man,but he must not support corrupt Siddaramaiah/CONG &amp; his insensitive Govt to public apathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# AND resort to dirty game of caste/Religion based politics,provoke youth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For first time gud Indian Muslims r speaking their minds.People like Geelani,Owaisi bros must be punished for their utterances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# By demanding reservation this illiterate buffoon has pushed Gujrat back by 50 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another joker who has developed Modi phobia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tribute to this great actor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has he got anything right till date of coronation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yrs, u will need 3 Janams to mature to reach Modi stature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why, seems u didn't get opportunity to deposit ur untaxed money in ur A/Cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She messed up UP &amp; stashed millions of illgotten money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She is angry as she didn't get chance to convert her &amp; Party ill gotten funds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Another pseudo secularists on prowl. He is insulting his own Religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does RG can recite even one sentence of Bhagwat Gita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In circus also people take selfies with clowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# MMS speak after getting brief from 10,Janpath. Why didn't he raised his voice against numerous scams done by UPA Ministers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since Yaswant Sinha is a disgruntled man. He will do great harm to his Party by even thinking of Rogue &amp;corrupt CONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has this child lost his mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If RG has better solution,why doesn't he debate with PM for sake of Country. Easy to do rhetoric but no constructive opposition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On one hand Modi trying sincerely to get rid of caste politics,but RG again at old CONG dirty game in Gujrat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We agree. Goondaism must not be tolerated at any cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is true respect to our brave hearts,not mere lip service as normally done by 3 Bollywood Khans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India find silence of 3 Khans on Rohingyas deportation quite interesting. Why?obivious bhai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sad to see Govt inaction on deportation of Rohingyas&amp;other illegal migrants. Big threat to National security.Creating filth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do u know rapid demographic change&amp;population explosion r biggest threat to India.Have u ever expressed ur clear stand.BIG NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Had u supported Govt in early deportation of dangerous Rohingyas,perhaps Majority might have tilted towards CONG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do u believe that without internal covert support,terror attacks continue to happen on Indian soil.THINK &amp;STOP APPEASEMENT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have u/family ever realized,how excessive Appeasement of Muslims have damaged National interests&amp;also their rightful progress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ur destructive approach will never bring CONG back to power.Only way to come back thru white papers on burning issues by CONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's ur stand on Rohingyas?Pl stop Appeasement&amp;don't play with sentiments of Majority. Keep ur dirty politics away from N Secu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Absolutely right.No point in talking to Rogue Nation,till they completely stop cross border terrorism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does he know the meaning of what he is uttering.Whole world laughing at his wisdom&amp;wits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Muslim Clerics r yet to demonstrate their will to fight against PAK Terror. Their Loyalty towards National security a big Q Mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Muslim sisters must insist for Gender Equality.Have fewer children.Focus on education&amp;health to ensure progress of their community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IndianMuslims must induct reforms in their Personal Law for their inclusive growth.Narrow thinking of more kids biggest drag on their growth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# FIRST CLEAN UR MIND ON APPEASEMENT.DELHI FAST TURNING INTO SLUM UNDER AAP RULE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Arnab urge u to start"DEPORT ROHINGYAS&amp;ALL OTHER ILLEGAL MIGRANTS"Must continue till Govt Report back last one DEPORTED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ALL PAK ACTIONS R BIG SUSPECT.IN FACT ROGUE PAK ARMY NOT ONLY BIGGEST THREAT TO THEIR OWN PEACE BUT ALSO WORLD PEACE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TILL THE TIME POLITICS OF RESERVATIONS,APPEASEMENT END IN INDIA.ELECTORAL&amp;POLICE REFORMS,POPULATION CURBS DONE.NATION GROWTH DOUBTFUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Urge PC to visit Okhla,Jamia, NZM . Nobody follow traffic rules.Full encroachment. Why Police also practicing APPEASEMENT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SC judges who pronounced controversial judgement must come out&amp;see the Pollution levels caused by more dangerous items]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>