<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nadler and AOC want him to resign but like his brother they have no shameðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Greta you upset all the Commies on the LeftðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ben Domench is an honest man and not afraid to speak out. Love this guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump was not in a political position numbnuts ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because the Left can't keep cheating with an IDðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If it wasn't for your courage, he would have gotten away with everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You Commies are a jokeðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That Stimulus check was started by Trump. Who gave their check back on the Commie Left, DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hard to think there can be that many stupid people in the country. They all seem to be in Hollyweird tooðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, gas is up! Why do you care you moron!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Where have you been, were you a bad boy ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isn't that the truth!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget Mr. Potato Head and Dr. Seuss ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She was raised with money. Her father is a director. She was their only child in that marriage, sure she had everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We should all go to gab. Have you noticed all the people that left?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not people, just conservatives!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They blocked me from responding to youðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Next Sunday, March 14th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Austin is totally liberal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I notice all the women that bash Melania are homely as sinðŸ¥µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's called marrying beneath you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I attempted to reply to your tweet and Twitter blocked meðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Since you voted for Biden we'll excuse your stupidityðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can we sue Swalwell for sleeping with a Chinese Spy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump with all his worldly knowledge seemed naive with some people. Trusted the wrong ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seems like all liberals can point their fingers at Trump but not the idiot that's in office nowðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden was going to cure the Virus if elected, what happened. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Didn't Biden promise to cure it if he was elected? ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Aren't they! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because Libnuts have no God in their lives, anything goes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Isn't she from Bostonia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because it's funny #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, he's suppose to ask what he's doing there not take questions. DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you looked like that, wouldn't you STFU ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why would it give her the shakes ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why not, you're no funðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There's no hope for Michael MooreðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He could take a shower ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He'd be better keeping a low profile with his looks.ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just give him a dozen Krispy Kreme donuts and he'll be fine ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What planet are you living onðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Welcome to CommunismðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Notice no one really mentions it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, that is earth shattering! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Candace, too bad your morals doesn't rub off on the liberal freaks but when you're low life you just don't get it.ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yet, libs use the most atrocious language and are never suspended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's a huge disappointment. Wish I could get my money back that I spent in her theme park.ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are you sure someone didn't physically attack Romney?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Allowing illegals in that are Covid positive but calling the Texas Governor Neanderthal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Requisite for being a liberal is passing a freak showðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dolly is a liberal who backed BLM and criticized whites. Anything she says doesn't surprise meðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Eric keep tweeting, the Libnuts are having meltdowns! ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone got to himðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This man cannot call himself a Catholic. No Priest should administer Communion to himðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not sure about the male part but the moron is white. How he can make a statement like that and hold his head up is beyond meðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All the idiots on the Left come up with this nonsense and the idiot leaders on the Left go along with itðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because the radical Left says so. Their crap never ends, such a sick bunch of losers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Mr. Potato Head, Dr. Seuss, etc. When does this nonsense end ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Biden is an advocate for abortion, that is not Christian ðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Step down, you're destroying our country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Happy Birthday David. ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Send it to me on Message. Twitter is not allowing me to save it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If I ever get on Gab will look for you. Will miss you and your fur babies ðŸ˜¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's because the warped Democrats are in charge. They're the most screwed up mental misfits ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Twitter has been removing my followers for years. Use to remove between 10 and 30 a day. Recently took 2500!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The uglies on the Left care because Melania is beautiful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She's not a Medical Doctor ding bat. Stop putting a beautiful woman like Melania down because you're ugly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They both had Covid, you're a liar and you have all these lefty idiots believing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because the Left are more like Commies. They are anti American. A sick bunch ðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget to add, and they want everything freeðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did someone beat him up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Another brain dead freak from L.A.ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What about Trump numbnuts ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell him not to worry, he's only whiteðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What is Biden doing for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't be, he would have gotten away with murder if it weren't for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, I am starting to lose some followers from yesterday but they already deleted 2500 a few months ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is crazyðŸ¥º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A press conference, he didn't know why he was in TexasðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How nice if someone gave that jerk a black eye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He didn't even know why he was in Texas ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where do all these liberal idiots come from on Twitter ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Forgetting when he was elected tooðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Democrats can't cheat thenðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ted, Ted, Ted, yes she does she's on the Right not the Commie Left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because most of them want freebies and they're not getting them fast enough ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We Floridians love DeSantis. You're showing your ignorance ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, makes Florida even better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can't beat Florida! A red state with the best Governor. N.Y's leader are a disgrace ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like he already is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Listen moron you better worry about your buddy CuomoðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you for being the best President. We miss you and feel the country's safety net is gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WOW! Give me a chair before I faint. Pelosi actually admitted a Democrat is guilty of something ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am and many others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're talking to a jerk from the UK, don't waste your breath!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why are you foreigners so ignorant. Looks like you have enough of your own problems so please, STFU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's very annoying some loser wins by fraud.ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It beats reading a teleprompter and still screwing up. You should be worried about Biden not Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes! We the People do not want RINOS in our party. If the corrupt Dems can stick together we should!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She also ran for the bottle to stop her shakesðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Liberal judges that are as bad as the rest of the Demonrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bill, it's former President Trump what's with the Mr. ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're jealous because Biden acts like a weakling. Trump's strength gauls all you libnutsðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Barack Obama! You're not stupid enough to think Biden is making the decisions now are youðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Commiefornia, makes sense why you are an idiotðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watching a man speak instead of mousy Joe is so refreshing. Realize how really bad he is missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love our President Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm watching our great President Trump and tweetingðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I stand corrected. Please accept my apology ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Today is the 27th. Biden was President a month ago. You feeling stupid yet, DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our incredible President TrumpðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You foreign moron, STFU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He loves his country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Shitter doesn't like free speech!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, Cuomo looks pretty badðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree, Cuomo is finished!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# True. Cuomo killed thousands in nursing homes an apology wouldn't cut itðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hey ding bat Mary, why not hold Cuomo responsible? Oh you forgot that would make senseðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, you voted for a guy that doesn't know where he is half the time. Smart move NumbnutðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For votes. Libs don't care about them personally, just want to give them citizenship so they'll vote Democratic ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because she's a Hollyweirdo CommieðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why you voted for the biggest Racist there is, Biden ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't wait to hear him speak after listening to that weakling mouse BidenðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrats, they're always looking for handouts ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully he or she is with a another loving ownerðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He only promised to cure the Virus to get elected and you numbnuts believed himðŸ˜ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜…ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the middle of Biden's speech, he asked where he was. This is not funnyðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He should have stayed on his peanut farmðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Biden is not fit to be President that is the problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden asked where he was in his speech in Houston. He's mentally failing and they're scared!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes! Eat no red meat but chicken occasionally. Mostly meatless dishes. True Vegetarians do not eat any meat or dairy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As a Jew you should be thanking Trump for what he did for Israel! Why are you so ungrateful? ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Since no one stops them, they'll continue to run the country into the ground. DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? I like to think he's a Democrat because he's an odd ball ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unbelievable what they get away withðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He has to be a DemocratðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still looks like a man with long hairðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, that's how stupid the Left isðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Stir up your brain. He was not impeached, DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's time to call it a day, you wore out your welcome. You're useless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you're a Hollyweirdo looney tunes that's what you doðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Incurable Yeast Infection is her problem ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't let this coward get away with what he's done. You are our hero!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Really? Swalwell slept with a Chinese spy, how dumb are youðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Plastic surgery does wonders!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Biden had five decades to do something but never accomplished anything except to get rich ðŸ¤‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden claimed if he was elected, he would cure the CovidðŸ˜„ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜…ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's not Hunter, where are his pictures? He was thrown out of the service for cocaine ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I want to see Biden's taxes since he's been ripping the country off for decadesðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, the Demonrats are above the lawðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, she is definitely an idiotðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You missed your calling as a stand up comicðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Get your eyes checked ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She was his baby sitter numbnuts and was married to someone elseðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always say you know how to get the Commie Left out of their rat holes. Listen to their meltdowns ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜…ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, only 75 million Americans voted for Trump. Biden won by fraud let's face it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We love your father. Biden is like a weak puppy next to him. We went from a man to a mouse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was okay for her father to start a phoney war. Wonder how she feels about that ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We the People do not care about Cheney's opinion. Trump 2024!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, too bad! Another turncoat ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Think it will sink in his headðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump is a man and Biden is a mouseðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're too stupid to respond toðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No, he's too denseðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Jesus was a Jew numbnuts. Yes some Jews have blue eyes, DUH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, Tiger lives in my state. Have been to his restaurant many times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most of the Libnuts are brain dead. None of them get it. They're all low IQ individuals, no hopeðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Their too stupid to know they were dupedðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah the knew one wants to circle around when you ask her a question. WTF does that mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I lost 2500 followers. The more I can get the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter took 2500 followers. Any ideas how I can get them back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Changing the subject always works with the Left. Have a nice day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did our wires get crossed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Clooney dated Ghislaine Maxwell too. What does that tell youðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The RINOS deserved a dump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounded like you were insulting Florida. You repeated what someone who was said??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why did you say "I'm sorry you feel that way"? Could have fooled meðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# At least you're an honest Democrat, not too many of themðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been to Indiana. Florida is paradise. IndianaðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Everything that had nothing to do with Covid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why didn't you discuss this with Obama who started the cages ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Should have told Obama who started the cages. What were you afraid ofðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, we noticed Biden likes kids ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You should have complained to Obama who started the cages during his administration ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Nice try you idiot? Why not fact check it, what are you afraid of getting a little intelligentðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you aware that Obama started the cages during his administration? Why are all you Lefties so brain deadðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, a little Dementia is nothing ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obama started the cages during his administration. Why is that not mentioned??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why didn't your boy Biden go to Texas the way Trump did. Why do you numbnuts give your evil party a passðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Where did the Flu go? I know there's a Virus but think the Dems have exaggerated the numbers since day one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We have had not one family member or friend that have had the Covid. Feel very lucky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reminds me of a walking Cadaver ðŸ‘½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Did he/she have his/her male organs removed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She was a he practicing Pediatrics. If that isn't scary, what isðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Absolutely! Everyone we are aware are Commies are boycotted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's have another trial with him and Ford. I defended this bumðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He considers himself a Catholic. Wonder what the Catholic Church considers him. Let's hear from the Bishops, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't you get earthquakes? UGH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe our President!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Feel so lucky to live in Florida with Ron DeSantis as our Governor!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>