<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is pretty fucked up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you are saying that I shouldn't vote for either you or Bill?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are all traitors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Put on your covid mask, go color or pet you security llama. The grownups are busy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is politically dead to us now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never surrender never retreat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trapper you are a twit! You all didnt listen to 75 million Americans so this what you get. Shame on you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guess they should have listened before it came to this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not neo anytime sir. Just everyday folks who you refuse to listen to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember sir, those are black folks too, regardless they are standing up for your rights to have an opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You know where you don't have to sit too closely with anyone else? Your car. Drive next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you Senator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# don't send money to foreign countries while Americans are suffering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can't beat a good oatmeal pecan cookie and I make the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No you can see the clip on YouTube. The Chinese translated it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep that sure looks like a guilty face doesn't it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# What about this? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The photo is not Gina by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That is fucked up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Release the hounds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I stood up and clapped at your closing statement. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree, DECLASSIFY EVERYTHING, DUMP ALL DOCUMENTS and FIRE the DEEP STATE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I challenge you to do a flyover and troll the #HASHTAG# rally in #HASHTAG# in Florida today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Joe did not know as he said he was, then he is too stupid to be president. If he did know then he is a liar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So are the "voting police" going to drag millions of people out of their homes and force them to vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just because no laws were broken does not mean it was okay to peddle influence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If he hasn't done shit in 47 years why do you think 4 more years is going to be different?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So all her body guards just have to stand in the pouring rain so she can stand up there being lame? Wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop f--king around Nancy. We need help out here!ðŸ˜–ðŸ˜¡ðŸ¤¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow! That is impressive. Would that be awesome if he won California.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am done with #HASHTAG# I am moving to #HASHTAG# where I am not blocked or censored. Twitter is dead, they just haven't realized it yet. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# More info. Is coming !!!!! #HASHTAG# Govt is involved in all these. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks, this was today in Toledo. It is now just sad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# mistake was that she generalized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So Ann, still not over being left behind by the Trump train? Just let it go and Breathe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# here is a little gem for your Saturday show. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the #HASHTAG# no longer relevant #HASHTAG# said that no one pushes #HASHTAG# around, yeah no one but his nurse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank God the video cut off or next we would have seen the Stay Puft marshmallow come bounding out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the option to #HASHTAG#. These brave girls have. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen brothers! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why Trump has requested all covid data be sent to the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case you are unsure, you can still choose to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Say hello to your Daddy when you get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FUCK YOU!!! And your nose too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time for the Republicans to "Stand up, stand out and stand for" #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When the swamp gets drained even those lounging on lillypads sink to the bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Beto needs to be reminded that we have ammo too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good luck with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't boycott the debate, use it as a platform to expose the DNC and media fraud that is happening again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Back in your cage monkey boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is a classic Freudian Slip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video tape is a beautiful thing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And you are still an ignorant #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we going to stand for this without push back? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see any difference at all. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My wife and I both agree that you should NOT sign this bill! Don't do it! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My welfare check again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: When are the people behind the Steele Dossier going to go to jail for lying to the FBI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Close it. We demand to be heard. Build the wall. MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These numbers make no sense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can you explain the math here? This makes no sense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We want a wall in our stockings. Ho ho ho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We want the wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don't have a clue do you? We like and agree with those people out here in flyover America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We want the wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then give us the wall. Done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then agree to build the wall. Done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW MAP: Cost of Illegal Immigration, By State #URL# via #USER# United West]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya just gotta watch this twice then retweet it. Seriously! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just finshed reading your book. Loved it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We had made up drinking games for the debates. Not sure I can drink THAT much.ðŸ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't care if they are left or right only that they are delicious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just read it. Loved it. I found it interesting, and inspirational.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is he eating a fish sandwich with onions? Because that would be way too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have a Nerry Christmas Dana. We appreciate your work very much at our house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Michellis acting like she is on an episode of "Washington Housewives". Sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We love you at our house Leah! Keep up the good works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is the gift that keeps on giving. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh no you "di dant"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We aren't allowed to criticize #HASHTAG# because she is a "woman of color" but "incompetence has no color". #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# equals #HASHTAG# it is time to take the down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have guessed that when #USER# said we would get tired of all the #HASHTAG# that he was talking about the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't put it past #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG# to be behind this. The timing is much too convenient. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What a sick mother fucker you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We are pissed off because we hate your smell of dog shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is the FBI Investigation of Blasey-Ford? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daughter Of CIA Assassin Paymaster Tries To Bring Down Trump Supreme Court Nominee Kavanaugh - #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No anger. No fear. No trama. Not until 35 years later. Ooookay? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tony, Do you know where this picture was taken?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok Joe, so what is you position now? Make your position known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegal Aliens, illegal aliens, illegal aliens, #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG# is a #HASHTAG# and your beard looks stupid but it fits for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in something even if it makes you an IDIOT, #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh I don't know, maybe those people ought to stop writing bad checks, and stealing shit. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funniest ass beating of the day. #HASHTAG# Way to go kid #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone really think McCain is an American hero compared to Neil Armstrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The winner of #HASHTAG# #USER# for her amazing idea to document the undocumented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say that #HASHTAG# , head of the new #HASHTAG# may run again in #HASHTAG# . That is a gift that #USER# dreams about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe that the sleeping giant just got #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is amazing what all you can get accomplished when you start your day with #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I saw that musical: "Beautiful" It was great. Pay for your own billboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would tell the CEO of YETI to remember whose trucks their coolers sit in the back of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wanted to get a #HASHTAG# cooler but now they don't interest me in the least. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Amen POTUS. Keep draining the swamp. I just love hearing the slimy creatures squeal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nice fair and balanced #HASHTAG# Arming teachers isn't about being a cop, it is about survival! #HASHTAG# is Americans protecting freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# with the term women being banned from #HASHTAG# maybe we will also have to ban all of the el and la from spanish language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a story that you may want to investigate &amp; report on is the open call for #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# The MSM is silent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder, did Rachael Madcow do an entire segment on how wrong she was?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is a good thing for Joy B that we are Christian. We HAVE TO forgive her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just because you may believe you are #HASHTAG# doesn't mean it's true. We know it is lie &amp; you are disgusting. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Oakland coffee shop should put a sign outside that says they are a #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# zone. That would end well, not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget to consider #HASHTAG# of new laws, ones that creates criminals out of normal gun owners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I supported you thru thick &amp; thin but if you follow the Dems &amp; the gun control crowd, I am through with you. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# can be solved by putting small biometric gun safe in every classroom. Perp can't tell which teachers have guns or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# should only agree to interview with #HASHTAG# if ground rules are the same as #HASHTAG# interview with #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really #USER# "deputy escapes death...again" Just a bit over dramatic. The second time the car just drove away. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who rents more cars, the #HASHTAG# that want a #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG# members? You made choice &amp; mine is #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I graduated in 1975 and we all had access to guns but nobody shot up schools. We have to focus on what's changed since then to solve problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This might help to grapple with a trillion dollars. One trillion dollars = 621 miles of $100 bills stacked up. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: BREAKING: The Democratic Memo has just been leaked ðŸ‘‡ #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Studio headlines like these are why we stopped watching you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watching Curling and drinking DW. Perfection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We are looking forward to seeing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't let the prison door hit you on the ass on the way in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still love you but sure you have come to regret that offhand comment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could not care less about a movie! It's just a movie man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unfortunately those who threaten never go. Maybe they are waiting for Rosey and Chealsy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw on #USER# that #HASHTAG# are threatening to leave USA if #HASHTAG# isn't passed. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you think that it is possible to get new pictures of #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# ? It is time, please, please, please. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# should turn the #HASHTAG# over to the #HASHTAG# to review &amp; redact. Don't fall into the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget about the second Indianapolis tragedy with death of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your coffee is like taking Aderol, one cup and I am good all day, but is delicious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Love these ladies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: You could watch this forever and never stop smiling. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is a pathetic. His fingerprints are on the #HASHTAG# Not #HASHTAG# just sad &amp; broken old man. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You nailed it on all counts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# gives 100k employees $1000 bonus. Doing the math for #USER# that's $100 million worth of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got a hat this week! It rocks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark my words #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# are dirty and will soon be implicated. This corruption is deep &amp; wide &amp; far from over. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I means she is a beautiful, stylish, and tasteful women. Why are you always trying to tear her down? Sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? Way to go positive! Apparently the "lawmakes" you talk to are the ones sitting on their hands walking out or who stayed home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We can only hope so. We hired Trump to #HASHTAG# He is draining it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's how we know we are winning. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You need to broaden your information on manufacturing. Sadly inaccurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like she is preoccupied with picking that $1000.00 CRUMB out of her teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We can be tough on NOKO but sympathetic to the plight of its enslaved people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The voters will reveal how powerless they really are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Loved every word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We loved ever word. Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# gets it and the dems don't. #HASHTAG# is the new mantra of our time. Great #HASHTAG# &amp; full speed ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job on #HASHTAG# #USER# don't worry about the Dems, they wouldn't support you even if you pardoned #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you should #HASHTAG# directly after the #HASHTAG# to mute #HASHTAG# &amp; the democratic response. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Thiiiiis is gonna get ugly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Shifty Schiff is shifting his pants right now because of that memo. Must be a hell of a memo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He will probably end up in a park elsewhere after suicide. He'd better keep his gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, I heard they were on too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Schiff is such a Dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I watched you on #HASHTAG# and have to ask, are stupid or just naive? Regular people understand, you look pathetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# watched you on #HASHTAG# today &amp; you knocked it out of the park. Yes, the American people are interested &amp; want to know. Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If people are not impressed by Trump at that table they don't deserve an opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Bernard? Get a clue! You obviously know zero about anything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 9th district wants the House to #HASHTAG# I am sick &amp; tired of the corruption &amp; deceit in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We still love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very telling that there has not been a leak of the 4 page classified unmasking memo. 100's of republicans saw it but only one democrat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #USER# wanted to bring democrats to heel quickly, just don't pay furloughed government workers for days off during shutdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did democrats protect #HASHTAG# Elian Gonzalez when Bill Clinton's SWAT team grabbed him at gunpoint and deported him to Cuba? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not about #HASHTAG# it is about #HASHTAG# No mystery, get an education, work hard and anyone can achieve their dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If building the wall would have no effect on illegal immigration, why do the democrats protest so much? The wall will work. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You did an excellent job on Fox and Friends. Hope you get that seat. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I vote for you to take that old bay's seat. Maybe wipe it down first though, it is probably musky. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is this For? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click the pic to get the joke. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Obama had to say about imagration Obviously he is a racist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 100% class act in the face of silly liberal drama. ðŸ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Love this idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To be fair she always looks like she is desperately trying to hold in a fart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You nailed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I watch any channel but Fox I feel like I have entered a Bizzaro World dystopia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know exactly what you said in your "private" #HASHTAG# meeting but thank you for saying it. This PC must be stopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# don't forget that surely the Elites are taking their family vacations in exotic places like Haiti and El Salvador.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Keep calm and eat buffet ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The moment you realize that Oprah didn't bring you here for a free car... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Harry Reid admit to telling the FBI to lie to then candidate Trump and disseminate fake news. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Remember, when you're protesting sexual assault -- always dress like a pirate hooker ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But...I want a free car.ðŸ˜®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe the real issue is why the hell they are spending that much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a trick. You know that right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do I get a free car?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looks like a bad case of chlamydia in want of some ointment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Some of us always believed you JB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why aren't the Dreamers mad that the Democrats are using them as a weapon to bludgeon Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We turn off the half time show. Too nasty, too political, too Hollywood. Just watch the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She did and excellent job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#books Truth or fabrication, Trump is still winning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No but there are some folks at your network that REALLY need some help over coming Trump Derangement syndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Hollywood has somehow managed to turn a scandal of its own making into three more hours of colossal self-righteousness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So wrong on so many levels. His face says, "Ahh...Mom? Are you down with this?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet that #HASHTAG# will have a hard time explaining this one away. Or I suppose not since it is Queen Oprah. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like maybe a bad case of Chlamydia! That's going to need some ointment. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes! Directly! Thank God for the Trump agenda. #HASHTAG# Dumping in necessary regulations, re investing in manufacturing, lower taxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Obama in 2008: "Hillary is a corrupt Wallstreet mogul" Obama in 2016: "No one is more fit to be president." ðŸ¤”]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>