<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh my god I heard of pangolins but that just looks awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fair enough, I think I at least understand the whole thought process now. Thanks for talking. 🎄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't name anyone that would fit the concept for the lefty side today. Greta Thunberg maybe? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How's the progress on the Team-Up variant+ashcan bundles? If I don't see anything this week should I email ya?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuck it, just take it and don't make a big deal about it afterwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# *or anything weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Live with Alex Jones and Owen Shroyer on the War Room! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah Tucker's always been good on these issues, but that's cool if he's been following along and get's it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# basically, Rand did nothing wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blackmail material has been sent to Mossad for safekeeping, and the bad man is dead. Case closed lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or the people that planned out and funded his enterprise, for that matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hahah no one's talking about killing, you clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Holy shit yes normies rise up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fucking bizarre the giant blind-spots these alt-light-ers have to perpetuate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hah, good marketing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People being loud in movie theaters? I might know some FBI statistics about that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit is all of the content pay-walled? fuck that nevermind lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Btw love your art style and looking forward to Sovereign!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That answers my question haha... I've only started following comicsgate and all related things pretty recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is the Liefeld Indiegogo project worth getting or is he just an asshole now? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor people are so dumb, don't you know you can take out loans and just never pay them back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Make him trans and you got a movie deal kid. 6 figures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tfw going back to The Shire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Low Birthrates? Nazi Germany Could Teach Modern Europe a Thing or Two #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My favorite Jewish comedian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that baby's name was Albert Einstein #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J CREAM- FINE WOMEN &amp; FINE THINGS (official video ) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: U.S. military issues warning to troops about incel violence at Joker screenings #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# STAYY THE FUCK BAAAACCCKK! WE WILL DEFEND OURSELVES! #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: He runs like he listened to his voters; but he governs by listening to Jared and Ivanka. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're the biggest and the gayest, folks. Russia doesn't stand a chance against Big Gay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Save up money while van-lifing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL! Gotta get that bag!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great speech Greta, very cool! Did you know I'm the King of Israel? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well sure, but women's rights were part of the beginning of society's problems, that led to incels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# EWJ videgame revival would be the best outcome. I don't wanna see EWJ in the MCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is good when there is an occasional hot female nurse around, but we need more male nurses in the industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At first I thought it said Dog Salem and was like "What's this, a Monster Hunter version of Dog the Bounty Hunter?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this comin to Netflix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HH Brother, The Hulkamaniacs will never be kept down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is wimmen empowerment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of them must be made black. Or make em a gay couple! I smell an Oscar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Expectations vs Reality #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And then everyone clapped!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Make Joe Rogan and Sam Hyde so I can make Sam choke Joe out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He also goes into our old friend Jussie at one point, loved that bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Damn, Ralph has to pay you more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why aren't you co-hosting you nigg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor white boys can't dance smh 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2020 will be the year of the Great Return!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow maybe people should stop migrating to white countries ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INVICTVS MMXX: Fireside Chat No. 1: On the System's Declaration of War #URL# via #USER# What a mad lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to #USER# live online via #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Book signings at the weigh-in! Drinks after the match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Certified Guaranteed Interesting #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think you should wear flat cap like guys in Peaky Blinders. It is more stylish but still very casual like beanie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Ninja Box - 4 Pillars To Building Ninja Schools Worldwide by Michael Yeh on #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Yes! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's about context. That context being the real world. Israel is the elephant in the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah it's actually not that bad, but I'm laughing at all the gratuitous nudity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was this one big gay op to bait Zoom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: South Africa explained in 28 seconds. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KENSHI Review | SSS Rank: Smuggling™ | Starvation™ | Slavery™ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TYT's Hasan Piker Praises Socialism, Open Borders, Islam—Blames Capitali... #URL# via #USER# lol, my sides are ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help make it happen for Warski And Ralph #URL# #HASHTAG# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should have #USER# debate Destiny. Get some Dick action in there too, lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks Paul, very cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Andy's been redpilled on the yellow Jew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love heterosexual white males]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BUILD THE ARTISTIC STEEL SLATS #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# lol and here I thought it was just the Jews disowning her for being ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Aww how cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wiggers should be sent to re-education camps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This guy has me questioning my biases against comic book movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think you've reached peak Bugmanism? Think again kid #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Grow up, Ironybros #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Do walls work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Real comfy Anglo hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nick will eventually embrace the Faustian spirit and become who we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should've used DJ Khaled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kenny vs Margaret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desmond is Amazing and this #HASHTAG# movement thing is a psyop to make Milo mainstream again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated superhero ideas: Black Israelite Superman. Wonder T-Girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Were they originally Nazifurs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Haha I think the whims of the current clique he's allowed in are more important to him than this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think he'd rather give debating Jim another try. Spencer owns suits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #USER# calls you a sweet dessert #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial opinion: I respect Baked Alaska more than Beardson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Michael Cohen Is Going To Prison — But At Least It’s Very Jewy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay straight, brothers. Don't go trans for e-fame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can I have like 5 bux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I eagerly await news of Chris Chan shooting up a theater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# NYC landlord is going on the list of hateful, anti-Semitic language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lol bet she was throwing shit at him. The woman cries out as she hits you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's like he did all that gay shit (the dildo stunt, Israel trip, etc) for nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why do only brown men get to be TransAge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now that's what I call top tier optics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# plus I've never tried to ruin you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Andy my fridge is empty can I have a few hundred too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They should do this to E-Sports players too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where's the lie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Is this the position of evolutionary biologist #USER# ? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop the car, get out and allow the unwashed masses to "know" you. (In the Biblical sense).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wtf, first degree murder? This is getting appealed, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS THE CIIIIIIIIIIIRCLEEE OF ORANGE MAN BAD FUCK WHITE PEOOPLLEE #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I made an AJ1 out of cardboard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The comments section, oof. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now THIS is epic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleb poorfags can't even into swindling sponsors into lending them millions of dollars. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's brown though, don't think this is gonna much press/outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ITS A MISTAKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Poofters and child groomers, for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh my mistake, I should have looked a little deeper into these things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can confirm, I bash Andy's low iq humor in chat all the time and never been timed out or anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give Alex Jones press credentials and sit him next to Jim Acosta #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallout 76: Bully Hunter #URL# via #USER# #USER# Game doesn't look too bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahah and she's in debt from ONE patron's refunds lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning and brave Macy's ad featuring white families and gay niggas! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Im looking forward to voting in Mexico, Canada, England, France and Germany’s elections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time should do a piece on the millions of weeaboos who are Japanese, just not legally. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: You guys.... wtaf. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IT'S A MISTAKE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have the kebab recipes! They can go back! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He say this nigga eatin beans 😂😂😎👌 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a few hundred years there will be INFINITE AFRICANS spreading across the universe and it will be beautiful #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Should all news stories be pre-approved by Donald Trump before they are broadcasted to the American people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Make white babbys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And the white race should be able to deny trans-white teens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How does one pay taxes when 20 of them will share the same SSN and apartment room? Oh yeah they mean sales taxes lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Are whites superior to others?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Donald Trump wants soldiers to open fire at the migrant caravan if they throw stones at them... Is that a good idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAAAASSSSS ISRAEL ROCKS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle East wars fawk yeah! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD FUCKING DAMN I CAME #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Should America only be white?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hail #USER# ! This Amazon Queen is leading hordes of beta bux orbiters to save the West. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh just checked again and he fixed his boomer tech issues and is talking about owning the SJWs- #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MILO LIVE, someone tell him about Gamergate 2.0! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Streamlabs will be hit. The ADL/SPLC can only censor youtube superchats, so they've gotta go after the alternative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actual Alt Righters would not be engineering these October surprises that only hurt the Right lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Pittsburgh thing is being used like a little mini-holocaust to make everyone love Jews again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got dead Jews so you know shit's about to go down. Gonna be civil war or WW3 or some shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: *immediately logs off* #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical crap-eating women #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# DID YOU JUST ASSUME THEIR HAIR IDENTITY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually it's kinda funny but I guess I have to include the whole globe in that statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can we just stop supporting arab, israelian and south american countries? I'm a nationalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Friends of Zion hosts event to honor Guatemala’s new ambassador to Israel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Makes sense, I understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shut up bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I believe what you're saying about them Andy, but to be fair you are a druggy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now now let's not speak too harshly, lest we accidentally become anti-semitic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Woah buddy you sound like an unhinged, ranting, drunk conspiracy theorist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You guys should come fight in LA, maybe #USER# could help set it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How do I start investing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What should my fursona name be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What do you want more? Please RT to get wide response]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["how do fix this and get my girlfriend to be ok with Dr. Peterson?" LMAOOOO 😂😂👌 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cut yuri completely out of your life, it is degenerate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sargon and Metokur are great leaders of men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nike's should only be stolen from now on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #URL# well here it it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gamergate 2.0 trigger the libs own the libs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That guy's memeing on real Boomer hours. *sips*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The optimal look is 3 days stubble so it's too late for him. May as well rock the neckbeard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gamers rise up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WE HAVE THE RECIPES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I could use a few k too, willing to send dick pics in return]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Woman Always Gets Best Ideas While Taking Shower With Two Jacked Dudes #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am Gundam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should infect everyone who comes over to leech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# never ended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well that's it, Kenny has won me over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Will do it sarcastically and then ruin it with my bad attitude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lol whaddya know there are results for him being a secret Jew on google. Props to him for being an explorer though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wut? A slave trader? Was Columbus Jewish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Critics" apparently hate Venom. Sign of a good movie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Connor is a libtard and Khabib is a kebab, yet we got Irishmen and Russians brawling. No more brother wars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Don't be a wine aunt; be a Wine Queen 👑]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you think there will be no leeches but then realize all globo-homo urban centers are the same #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get me on sale buy 1 get 1 free Asians but make sure they're fresh please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love fancy Drumpf parties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe he is the real Mossad operative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has happened mere days after following #USER# and helping speak out against Jewish influence on the anime industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my metal forks have mysteriously disappeared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shill's basement lmao #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sure thing chosen one 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kids in the Hall indoctrinated me into loving gays, before I became redpilled and became a trad-neet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's called autism. He can defend all his points intellectually. Sean will be stumped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# AIU believes in pedal powered head bashing machines as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sam Hyde popping in is like Kim Jong Un making a surprise visit to a North Korean town and kissing babies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# C R E D I B L E T E S T I M O N Y #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The mad man openly naming himself as a white male. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What incredible brave sacrifice! She must be telling the truth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Women like her believe they will get some action from men who resort to rape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for some paypigs, will send you pics of anime girls for every $100 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bleach the anime is one of the last stands of implicit white identity. Rare take. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SEND EM TO ISRAEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah but ur racist. ALL CRIMES ARE BAD AND ALL MEN ARE BAD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>