<author lang="en" class="0">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But these were the exact words from Maxine Waters D from CA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But these were Maxine Waters exact words against people who workfor Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he pulled a gun on the officer????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he pulled a gun on an officer, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands Rally In Baghdad To Demand U.S. Troops Leave Iraq #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Omar Khadr is giving a keynote address at Dalhousie University - The Post Millennial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killing the commander of the basij forces who is responsible for ethnic cleansing in Ahwaz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blood in his hands He personally organized the assassination of 40 thousand Iraqi former military personnel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford to invest $1.45 billion in 2 metro Detroit plants, add 3,000 jobs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialisim You believe me or I kill you #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump Was Right" Federal Government Disaster Aid Found Untouched In Puerto Rican Warehouses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# I know somebody is going to complain as usual. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 more Puerto Rico officials fired after discovery of warehouse full of Hurricane Maria supplies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders backed a party that supported Iran during hostage crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico governor fires emergency director after aid is found sitting in warehouse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Op-Ed: We Can No Longer Tolerate An Economic System Where The Rich Get Richer And The Poor Also Get Richer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Muslim refugee Dalia al-Aqidi announces she’s running against Ilhan Omar #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders Clarifies His Gulags Will Be Democratic Gulags #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Block A Vote To Support Iran Protesters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian security forces open fire at protesters in Tehran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course she opposed the deal. We need to vote her out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi journalist and cameraman are 'assassinated' after reporting on anti-government protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[183 Australians have been charged with starting bushfires this season #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abu Mahdi Mohandis "I am proud to be called a terrorist" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme leader is a killer Solimani is a killer From Tehran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranians chanting America is not our enemy Our enemy is here in Iran (The Ayatolla) Scott A McMillan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranians chanting that their regime is a copy of ISIS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The regime of terror #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranians chanting against the terrorist regime inside Tehran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Devil horns' eclipse over Middle East causing social media stir #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korean mum faces jail because she allowed Kim portrait to burn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record 158,803,000 Americans Employed; 1.85M Year-to-Year Increase #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is wrong with the democratic party. Why they think it is ok to regulate the lives others #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarcastic but very true #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Iran Policy Isn't the Problem; Obama's Was #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Don’t believe Iranian propaganda about the mourning for Soleimani #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the people from Iraq and Iran support President Trump Scott A McMillan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq consulate in Southfield to open for those mourning Iranian general's death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott A McMillan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ricky Gervais Just did it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marked Safe From #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump Is Doing The Right Thing, But He’s Doing It As Trump, Which Means It’s Still Bad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to terrorists: ‘We will find you, we will eliminate you’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shadowy Iranian spy chief who helped plan Benghazi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best customer service experience. They go the extra mile to do the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarcastic and super funny #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU calls for tampons in men's rooms in order to achieve 'menstrual equity' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in Spring Valley, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food stamp enrollment falls to 8-year low as Trump clamps down on fraud, economy improves #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. General Election 2019: Conservatives Headed for a Majority, Exit Poll Shows #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kit Mobile Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is so hot, it is snowing in the Sahara #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials: U.S. Navy seizes suspected Iranian weapons set for Yemen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI searching for terrorist from San Diego #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavco Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40 Iraqi Protesters Slain in 24 Hours as Violence Spirals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40 Iraqi Protesters Slain in 24 Hours as Violence Spirals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 anti-government protesters killed in 'one of the worst' days of clashes in Iraq | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calif. woman says gun saved life when home intruder broke in #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fling Mobile Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Staffer Exchanged Private Emails with Yovanovitch, Contradicting Her Sworn Testimony #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media partially unblocked in Iraq after 50 days - NetBlocks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Even Isis wouldn't shoot at us': medics on frontline of Baghdad protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It looks like a war zone': Our Observers report from inside Iran’s protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After decades of pushing bachelor’s degrees, U.S. needs more tradespeople #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine and drugs Gambling problems Woman issues And a 1 million dollar salary for doing nothing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lancer Homes Manufactured Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing 'Ghost Plane' Created By 800 Drones At Air Show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KIT Mobile Home For Sale in Spring Valley, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finland’s government collapses over failed health care reform #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego to experience 'summer, fall and winter' by late Tuesday, early Wednesday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Hundreds of Iraqis have been killed. The world’s silence is deafening. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahwazi Football Fans Beaten, Arrested by Iranian Forces for Supporting Iraqi Revolution - DUR UNTASH STUDIES CENTRE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian agents are trying to stir up a civil war in Iraq #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq protest death toll rises to 300 with nearly 15,000 injured #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fleetwood Manufactured Home For Sale in Escondido, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Iraq protesters mock security forces, the death toll keeps climbing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, continue to share #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a shame. How much did you get paid. I always though human rights organizations are a scam, you proved me right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's impossible to beat ISIS so long as Erdoğan remains in power in Turkey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you spare a minute to help Musab Jabar? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 13 killed as Iraq resumes live gunfire against protesters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A revolution is taking a place #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Iraq disaster #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq violated human rights in protest crackdowns that left 149 dead, UN report finds | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq violated human rights in protest crackdowns that left 149 dead, UN report finds | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Chappelle: Second Amendment exists ‘just in case the First one doesn’t work out’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at his best. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash-Strapped CNN Now Just Recycling Old Articles But Replacing 'Russian Collusion' With 'Ukrainian Scandal' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man arrested in attack against Syrian refugee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2019 Ozone Hole is the Smallest on Record Since Its Discovery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Who Slammed Trump for ‘Racist’ Immigration Policies Killed by Illegal Immigrant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A million people are jailed at China's gulags. I managed to escape. Here's what really goes on inside #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never liked straws anyway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Chinese are the ones taking oil, but also the gold and everything they get their hands on. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ayn Rand Quote #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly why I think CNN is biased to team Clinton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrat 101 Freedom of speach is for the people on left only You are not allowed to critique China #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Veritas’ alleged CNN whistleblower claims network is ‘pumping out propaganda' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madison Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism at its best #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas prices exceed $5 a gallon at some Los Angeles area stations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US puts visa restrictions on Chinese officials over abuses of Muslims in Xinjiang #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Widespread sniper fire' as death toll soars in Iraq protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq is under curfew and Internet blackout as government tries to curb protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California DMV error results in 1,500 noncitizens registered to vote #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations. New York has just surpassed California for having the dumbest law ever. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whyyyyyy Resources should not be wasted to help people make stupid decisions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13.5 Tonns of gold, and 40 Billion (with B) US dollars in bribes&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in Alpine, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least ‘10 dead and over 200 injured’ as riot police open fire on Baghdad protesters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even after CDC and FDA confirmed that all sick cases involved THC obtained in the black market #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl who said classmates cut her dreadlocks admits she lied #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schiff apparently pranked by Russian radio hosts who promised 'naked Trump' photos #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today at congress #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim Waffen SS praying (Slovakia, 1944) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the tip of the scandal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crocked family #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tulsi Gabbard: Transcript doesn't show 'compelling' case for impeachment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Majority of Americans don't want Trump to be impeached and removed from office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is most of the media circling the wagons to protect Hunter Biden? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fremont Police Tesla Near-Dead Battery Forces Officer Off Pursuit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Embassy pressed Ukraine to drop probe of George Soros group during 2016 election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madison Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Declares War on Lobbying, Hires Lobbyist One Day Later #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KIT Mobile Home For Sale in Spring Valley, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hudson: Greta Thunberg, Take Your Climate Tour to China; America’s Reduced Its Carbon Emissions for Decades #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change' Went Out The Window When 2020 Dems Descended On Steak Fry At Iowa State Fair #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative Activists Clean Up 50 TONS Of Garbage In Liberal Los Angeles; Media Silent #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider myself as a classic liberal. That is why I think the left has nothing to do with liberalism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration forces China to sell the Port of Long Beach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church pastor to air conditioning thieves: ‘It’s hot where you’re going’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to hit San Francisco with EPA violations over homeless waste #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS-13 gang member arrested after entering US illegally #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never hear they granted clemency to an administrative crime #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great man is gone. Very sad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren wrote 'American Indian' for race on 1986 bar registration, report says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don not believe in aliens but this is news #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to San Diego Mr. President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market's value under Trump has grown by $6.9 trillion to $30.6 trillion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a horrible government overreaching. I am one of those effected and I hate the new rule. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Force deal to refuel near Trump’s Scottish resort reportedly signed under Obama #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in Escrondido, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 convicted in Sacramento County killings receive clemency from Gov. Gavin Newsom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another win that will not be reported as usual. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Was Right: Feds Nab Top FEMA Admin. in Massive Puerto Rico, Hurricane Maria Corruption Scam #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They burry the important information so when you read the title... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Trump, Fed-Up With Dems, Orders White House Officials To Combat C.A. Homelessness #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the worst things ever suggested. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico says it has cut migrant flow by 56% #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice how democrats care so much about climate change that they forget to mention the only feasible option The nuclear option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford cancels Mexico plant, expands U.S. factory and adds 700 jobs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merced County Sheriff criticizes state sanctuary laws after deputy shooting suspect arrested #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the award for the worst neighbor goes to.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego's biggest weather event of the year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Paul's Latest Oversight Report Finds $50 Billion in Wasteful Spending - Pursuit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in El Cajon, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufactured Home For Sale in San Diego, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KIT Mobile Home For Sale in Spring Valley, CA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump plans to release JFK assassination documents despite concerns from federal agencies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs law to punish websites for sex trafficking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar Accused Of Having Affair With Married Man, Funneled Campaign Money To Him, Report Says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First the USMCA Now a new deal with China Finally someone knows how to bully the bullies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning This is a sarcastic article #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiat Chrysler will move Ram production to Michigan from Mexico #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Katyn Massacre: When Stalin Ordered The Execution Of 22,000 Men, Then Blamed The Nazis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After going woke and losing $8 billion, Gillette embraces masculinity again - The Post Millennial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businesses hiring real SF cops on OT to keep crime down, employees safe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman becomes first female Marine to pilot F-35B fighter jet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco board rebrands 'convicted felon' as 'justice-involved person,' sanitizes other lingo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man arrested while trying to fix flat tires with gauze, Band-Aids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Bithday my dear Friend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People on the streets of Hong Kong You showed us again, that freedom is priceless. Love and respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A positive thing in society See something, do something If you can help, please do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After murder rate passes NYC, London Mayor Sadiq Khan calls for sharper knife control #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philly protest will support suspect accused of shooting six cops: 'I don't understand it,' police commissioner says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a while, they Will be majority in some places #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And someone thinks gangs will stop owning guns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diegans file lawsuit challenging state assault weapon ban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half the 600,000 residents aided by NYC Care are undocumented immigrants #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coke is releasing two new holiday flavors, and we hope they're not gross #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Offers To Trade All Of Its Communists For Democratic Protesters In Hong Kong #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Healthcare is not working in Finland #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public option for healthcare🤣🤣🤣🤣 Government never produce anything of value cheaper than the private sector. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Foundation Failed to Disclose 1,100 Foreign Donations #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>