<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Where actual racism doesn't exist, they simply manufacture it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where actual racism doesn't exist, they simply manufacture it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: New Gab post: Natural Order of Mankind (not safe for Twitter NSFT) - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's certainly not clarifying that the attacks on Asians are being committed by blacks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because Jews have a lot more power and influence than anyone wants to admit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No way. Asians are currently blaming Whites for the violent attacks committed by blacks. Asians are not our allies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real hate crime that's taking place is blaming White people for what blacks are doing to Asians. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another black guy violently assaults an Asian person. Time to rally against White Nationalism, right? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon? It's already been no country for White men. Some of us have been trying to illustrate this fact for decades. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Jewish interests alway come first. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote and retweet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I used the one you shared. Thanks again, brother. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know. I don't have the app. I only use it through PC/desktop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Gab post: Natural Order of Mankind (not safe for Twitter NSFT) - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I could see them creating a human raft-bridge all the way across the Pacific. They've got the raw material, after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With a magnificent blond beard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, and Lord Indra attained GLORY that day. His name now lives on in eternal recognition by millions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't understand it at all, but I'm literally laughing out loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And who exactly gets to define what a "White supremacist" is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Selfishness really is a religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No group of people has had more money thrown at them than the black community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;"Billions in COVID relief for black farmers." Tell me again how we're living in a "White supremacist" society?... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: It's amazing how often Jews are involved in significant world events. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denying that you're racist is actually proof that you're racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now THAT's a bridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish interests alway come first. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing how often Jews are involved in significant world events. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's certainly not the White kids that are running around making my neighborhood unsafe at night. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So are we going to make the summer of 2021 the revival of boater hats, or what? I'm down if you all are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Great on so many levels. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says the Libtard. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blah, blah, blah. Same old shit, just a different day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you have a source for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Snake doge. Many such cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're free to support him all you wish, but no, he doesn't "deserve" support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You do know he's Jewish, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How did you manage to incur multiple feral Main Coon attacks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The blackwashing just never ends. White people are being erased, little by little. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a Millennial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great on so many levels. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, not at all. That sounds like more BS made up by people who hate him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That literally never happened. You're 100% lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What an excellent groyp &amp; credit to the presenter too ðŸ‘ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've twice had the honor of carrying the urn that contains his ashes, and even once holding his famous corncob pipe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Lincoln Rockwell Born 9 March 1918 Assassinated 25 August 1967 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always asking the opposite. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't see that as a "bright side". Race-mixing is race-mixing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race-mixing. Race-mixing everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blackwashing just never ends. White people are being erased, little by little. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should really look into how Rhodesia became Zimbabwe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yet men are judged as cowardly if they're hesitant about getting married in this age...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even gunfights used to be more cultured and classy once upon a time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;"Ferguson Activists Demand $20 Million From Black Lives Matter" Good, good. Let them devour themselves. Article - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No such barriers exist, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was an accident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Just in case they finally terminate my account, you can keep in touch with me here - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case they finally terminate my account, you can keep in touch with me here - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More big accounts being terminated. It's only a matter of time before they purge us all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aaaggghhh... Fug. F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I AM allow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it mental illness that makes these people so incredibly violent? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Healthcare worker" is a political position. A radical Liberal extremist political position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# WTF is going on? This world is nuts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[99% of the time, I leave my typos us as-is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autocorrect? More like auto-incorrect. I swear, my autocorrect changes words that I spelled completely right the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm on Gab and Odysee, that should be good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a bunch of hyperbolic drama queens. These politicians embarrass our entire country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very effeminate. Very girly. Very juvenile. Very gross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I post like a leader? Since when?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And these are the figures who hold all the power over the fate of the American people... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me again how "White privilege" is a real thing... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fired my first real gun when I was ten years old. 20 guage shotgun, slug. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# According to all of my German speaking friends, the Manheim translation is the most accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The war against Adolf Hitler never ended. It just evolved into a war against all White people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can never tell us how we're wrong... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure to follow my bro here over on Gab ðŸ‘‡ðŸ‘‡ðŸ‘‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They literally all do it. Even the ones who swear they don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are chicks always lowkey staring at their own ass when they think no one's noticing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: New Gab post: The Virus and Its Diseases - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aaaaggghhh... "Demolished"... Because of course they did...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact, drawing non-white figures at all is racist. But if you refuse to draw non-white figures, well yeah, you're a racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacists just keep getting darker and darker these days, don't they?... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't really do them a whole lot of good, did it? Seeing as they went so thoroughly extinct...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have transcended all of reality. What a trip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Her argument was "born that way" makes something healthy and/or valid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pro-White. Yes. That's not bigotry. It's protectionist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They do, actually. Their app is called LBRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very cool. What's it say in the upper righthand corner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a racist airline? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show us the way, Denmark. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odysee &gt; Bitchute and YouTube Follow me there - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She's not really gone if he still has to pay her debts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Gab post: The Virus and Its Diseases - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe you're talking about this recent Gab post I made - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yikes. Yeah, that's pretty disappointing. But that doesn't change my sentiments toward his children's books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were the absolute best. It was actually fun to read them. It never felt like a chore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why you skip the forward and jump right into the author's own words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatism is just Liberalism in sheep's clothing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're free to write a better book, if you think his wasn't the greatest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: New Gab post: Bio-Religious Commitment To Insanity - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't find an image that's high enough resolution to produce a poster size print that's sharp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The text reads: "The German composure, The German performance Behold The Nordic racial-inheritance!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am, yeah. Here's a list of links where you can find me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His little face is just bellowing out the words "hidden in plain sight", lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're free to mute or block me. That should do the trick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Gab post: Bio-Religious Commitment To Insanity - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've lost about 2500 in two days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Keep track of me here - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down over a thousand now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You and I both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, how far we have fallen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the only Twitter account I've ever had. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only account I've ever had here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The app for Odysee is called LBRY. Odysess is LBRY's desktop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And I for yours. Thank you for being a part of the good fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep track of me here - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there yet another purge taking place? I'm down another 600 followers as of this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They always end up blocking me shortly after launching an attack on me. Why are they all such cowards? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This chick just called me a douche bag... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what? He wasn't wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you in France or Germany?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is clearly targeted harassment and/or a veiled threat of violence. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: $400 per Gram #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm not old, then. I've got some years to go yet before I reach the big four-O.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Beags and I go way back. All the way back to the academy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every time I click to open pictures of puppers like this, I always click on the nose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How old is "old" ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# America is well on its way to becoming a solid second-world country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't like anime or manga. The Vinland Sagas are actual sagas written by Vikings a thousand years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And we're all Feds because we survived the purge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you read the Vinland Sagas, though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Lost 1200 followers. Twitter seems like a very tolerant, free-speech-loving place...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Gab account is exploding right now. Can't keep up with notifications over there. Gab - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ayo, RC, why you never get banned from Twitter?" Article I referenced in the audio - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprises here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost 1200 followers. Twitter seems like a very tolerant, free-speech-loving place...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just lost 200 in the last few hours. And during the last major purge, I lost 1400. This site is so fucking stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: How it started How it's going #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only this were really true... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I almost included it in the second tweet, but was pretty sure they'd ban me just for saying it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, I personally don't agree with either of them bombing Syria. Or any other Middle Eastern country, for that matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# May the Gods grant bless their battle, and may they be successful in their expansion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I sincerely hope it was. However, I'm sure it was used just to stir up more "White man bad" controversy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1) I've never been a Trump supporter. 2) So that somehow justifies Biden bombing brown people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who's "MaxO" ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How it started How it's going #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As if Netflix isn't already a raging machine of diversity propaganda...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet you just bombed a Middle Eastern country... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They prove us right, every single time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden: "We don't need another war in the Middle East" Also Biden: *Proceeds to bomb Syria* #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember way back in the day when it was the Left who protested against meaningless wars? How the world does change...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brace for impact...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: New Gab post (unrelated) - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Gab post (unrelated) - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honesty Loyalty Maturity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hers look all flabby and droopy, though. Nothing appealing about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Her meltdown is all for show. She doesn't really care. She's just an attention-wh*re trying to get views and likes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would happily adopt her cat if it's in need of refuge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I sympathize greatly with her cat. I'd be happy to offer the cat refuge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is some top-tier photo shop action. Love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More and more of our people are bailing out of YouTube and switching to LBRY/Odysee - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is satire, right? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Computers can't tell the difference between a lot of things. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lead the way, then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: New comic by Hedgewik (his account is locked atm) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone's going to want to pay attention to this. Ramifications could be immense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discrimination against White people, inbound. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow, stunning and brilliant argument there. Totally disproved his point. Not really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those White supremacists keep getting darker and darker, don't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Our mere existence is an unforgivable offense to these creatures. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to see here, folks. Just diversity continuing to be our greatest strength. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to break it to you, bimbo, but not every guy on the planet wants to sleep with you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those White supremacists just keep getting darker and darker, don't they? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our mere existence is an unforgivable offense to these creatures. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, this looks like it was computer generated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dude's a fucking robot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Why's it just assumed he's fighting back? How do we know he's not the one who actually started the fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a fucking king.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video deserves every thumbs-down it gets. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or why not go ahead and make Rhodesia great again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again, Libertarians prove that they're actually just diet Liberals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The global war against White people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People don't fake hate-crimes for free government money, do they? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So you're justifying the theft of White art?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Joe Biden's message to White people is clear: death is good for your health. Suicide equals survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why's it just assumed he's fighting back? How do we know he's not the one who actually started the fight? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a foreign country have control over US aid budget? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The global war against White people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually it's going to be considered "racist" for any White person to deny non-whites access to their body. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Truth, as it were. Can't be having any of that wrong-think going on around here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When White people say that Jews aren't White, it's considered anti-Semitism. But when Jews say it themselves... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's literally the only institutional racism that exists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For whatever it's worth, Merrick Garland, by his own admission, is Jewish. Just a point of fact, nothing more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# It's racist to hold non-whites accountable for their actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's racist to hold non-whites accountable for their actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Frustrated teen victim of White supremacy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Batman is a fiction character, though. FiCtIoNaL cHaRaCtEr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't forget about the big sheet of chewy bubblegum they hide under the carpet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did you just tweet @ your man from bed, so that he'd make you coffee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a random note, I reached a new top speed on Lumosity game Highway Hazards. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>