<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A blunt is required right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can take the boy out the hood but you can never take the hood out the boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to get back in the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mood went from bad to PISSED OFF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate my job. I'm quitting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I advise no one to piss me off today unless your mouth wants to meet my fist a couple few times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different day SAME MOTHER FUCKING BULLSHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the type of dude that would rather stick you in the mouth than try and talk things out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This money can't fit in my pockets but I bet that gun fit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry not sorry its in my blue blood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a dollar for every time a mafucka to me I'm white and to stop talking/acting black I'd be on that bill gates status]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter where life takes me I will always stay true to what I know. That thug mentality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND THAT BLUE BANDANA IS THE TEAM FLAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thing called work would be SK much better if I was fucking high as shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work. Can. Suck. My. Dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't I be rich? I fucking hate waking up to go to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, im done. Got work in 5 hours. I'm fucked. Goodnight. Prepare for my 5am Twitter BITCHING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I know you're fuckin with me.. this is something my 5 month old son would say... "#USER#: bawang putih bawang merah"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SORRY I DO NOT SPEAK TOWEL HEAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mannnn I really fucked up by following 1.6k people out of boredom the other day lmao. now all these mafuckas talking god knows what language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVRTYTIME ME AND MAGGIE FIGHT SHE HAS TO FUCKING BRING UP ADRIENNE LIKE BITCH I DONT HOLD LUCAS, RONNIE, ANTHONY, ETC OVER YOUR FUCKING HEAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch me take this 9 to all of your dome pieces. Real shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond fucking HEATED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test me Nashville Tennessee please test my limits. Watch how many innocent people you lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck around with my 5 MONTH OLD SONS health and refuse to solve the problem? I WILL put a bullet in your forehead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch what happens when Aiden catches it. I swear to God you will regret the bloodshed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The city of #HASHTAG# has said they will not be doing anything about the #HASHTAG# in our neighborhood .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our neighborhood tested positive for west Nile virus. I swear to Jesus himself if MY SON gets this shit I will murder the city. Bet me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# thank u :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try and deepthroat ill fuck around and choke ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sell me some cocaine now "#USER#: #USER# yourself very welcome, Mr. Allen."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omgzzzzz thank you for correcting me. #HASHTAG# English teacher "#USER#: #USER# it's gonna be alright. we can get through this."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!"" I MADE A TYPO!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# aww referring to yourself as a nobody ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# y do you look like a failed abortion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# who r u cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# now. Don't come at me sideways again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# everyone who likes a blunt and funny mother fucker should give this feller a follow ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when the faggot daus he wants to piss on the grave of a woman who died during labor I could give a fuck less what happens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# That is the most polite way I've ever heard someone request a suicide. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# who the fuck says they want to piss on the grave of a woman who died during labor? Idgaf if im an ass. The BITCH should die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blowjob and a blunt sounds perfect right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I. Want. Head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Im Still Gonna Smoke.. Wether It's Legal Or Not ~.~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you're legit fucked up in the head my nigga. Kill yourself. Please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If youre speaking some foreign language, or if you're blowing up my TL with the followback stuff prepare to lose a follower. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now I start the long task of unfollowing all you faggots who don't follow back -_- S/O to all my followers doe. ^_^ √√√√√√√√√√]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: ...Retweet if you Follow Back…"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for S/O's. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# doing all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All yall unfollowers have til morning to follow before I unfollow that ungrateful ass. Jus sayin. I appreciate all y'all follow back niggas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up early in the morning eat that pussy like cold pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Boy: Hi. Girl: I have a boyfriend. Boy: I said hi, not suck my dick."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# no problem (:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: SHOTOUT TO #USER# CONFESSION YOU KEEP IT 100]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: SHOTOUTS WITH A CONFESSION #HASHTAG# DOIN ALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: At least clean up the bathroom before taking your profile picture in there."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# thanks . Shhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# give a nigga follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# go follow herrr!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# everyone ahould follow this eye candy (:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# er'body should follow her :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/O to #USER# go follow him NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the nigga #USER# follow him for some cold ass rap with some beast ass beats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for a shoutout :) doing all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I DON'T GET WHY PEOPLE WHO HAVE YO NUMBER RATHER MESSAGE YOU ON FACEBOOK OR TWITTER INSTEAD OF JUST CALLING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anytime bro mention me when you get more music always down to listen to aspiring artists "#USER#: #USER# I APPRECIATE THE HONESTY"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# verses are good but I had to turn it off because the chorus got annoying actually. Not being rude lol but 5 words repeated 20 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank yewwwwwwww :D "#USER#: { #USER# } Icon: 9 Bio: 10 + Header: 10 your baby is cute x"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: { #USER# } Icon: 9 Bio: 10 + Header: 10 your baby is cute x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my hiphop lovers take a second to listen to this Its actually decent as fuck. Real shit #URL# ic/JAyBoY+HeNdriX?l=0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT for a rate Icon: Bio: Header:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[265 new followers ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# haha hey thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# followers* is spelled with two "L's" not one. ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I SPEAK ENGLISH MY NIGGA "#USER#: #USER# no me dejes de seguir"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish i could understand half these towel heads on my TL. I feel like I'm overseas now. FML lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: New day same bullshit."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao. Holy SHIT man. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: I FUCKING HATE BEING INTERRUPTED!!!!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing I have this app to tell.me who follows then unfollows so I can get rid of yo asses &gt;:|]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[154 new followers I'm the past hour hahahahahaha. Only problem is now my TL is like Arabic people :( can't understand SHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about some new followers ;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I FOLLOW EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU CUTIEPIES BACK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone go follow #USER#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you da man ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Everyone go follow #USER# now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SORRY FOR BLOWING YALL UP WITH THIS FOLLOW BACK SHIT BUT I WANT MORE FOLLOWERS HEHEHEHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Retweet for a tipsy shout out? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: I Feel Like Getting High .."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: &gt;&gt;&gt; Retweet if you Follow Back &lt;&lt;&lt;"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: #USER# how?!?" Retweet the #USER# tweets haha. 53 new followers so far. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: ✰ⓇⒺⓉⓌⒺⒺⓉ✰IF✰YOU✰FOLLOW✰BACK✰ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 08.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 new followersin 2 minutes? I can dig it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha oh wow. I can sell my Twitter account for $130 lmao. Who the fuck buys twitter accounts tho? Thirsty individuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish twitter had a mute button.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HELLLLLLLLL NAAAAAAAAAAAAA "#USER#: literally the most embarassing thing i've ever seen.. #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: #HASHTAG# ignore the rude people who talk behind their back. That's exactly where they belong, behind their back."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Men are biologically wired to fall asleep after sex." Or during hahahaha #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a wild boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All his blood his spilled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when we ride around bitches follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't make me go pop the trunk. On you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to see you smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: RT IF YOU FOLLOW~BACK &gt;&gt;&gt; Follow anyone who Retweets this and Gain Instant Followers….."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imma have to download the emojii app again just so I can start thumbs uppin' these mother fuckers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[drug money. buy you whatchu want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THATS A CUTE MOTHER FUCKER "#USER#: The animal in the Firefox logo is not actually a Fox. It's a Red Panda. #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep in my heart i know that you love me as much as I love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayin for daylight waitin for that mornin sun so i can act like my whole life aint goin wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit like this is why i drink lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd be 5 this July ;(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could have been. What would have been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This song always reminds me of you little guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though memories fade I got your name tatted on my arm so be both ball til my dying days. #HASHTAG# :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drank a fifth for that ass when you passed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screamin thug til I die til i pass out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in peace young nigga there's a heaven for a G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hahahaha ;) doing what we gotta do my nigga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the fuck cares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't fuck with hoe Niggas. I camt trust these hoes neither]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imma shine homie until my heart stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna live good so shit I sell dope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate it or love it the underdog on top]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maggies dad said I'm white and not ghetto the other day. I had to laugh my ass off to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still the thug that you love to hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab your glocks when you see Tupac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Never plan for tomorrow cause today might be your last day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# where THE MOTHER FUCK HAVE YOU BEEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ain't no killer but don't push me. Revenge is like the sweetest joy next to getting pussy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm addicted to the rubber bands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckin wit a nigga meet my mother fuckin goons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never kill a woman unless she a witness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggies Ten Crack Commandments speaks the truth about the game. Real shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know you heard this before, never get high on your own supply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I been in this game for years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see you bitches talk in loud but you ain't sayin shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son is screaming blood murder bc he cant have this pixie stick. Lmfao wow lil nigga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and me baby we're stuck like glue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Said I'm not your cup of tea? Can't you tell I'm a fucking G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: A #HASHTAG# charisma and good nature are hard to pass up."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son is obsessed with flowers omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need. More. Music. Help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Everything is funny as hell when its not happening to #HASHTAG#."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DYING LMAOOOOOO "#USER#: #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I NEED COUNTRY ARTISTS NAMES OR SONGS SO I CAN DOWNLOAD MORE MUSIC. HELP! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Music #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downloading sooooo much damn throwback music right now lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K no more tweeting. I'll be pissed if i get my phone wet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naked soakin wet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to put a #HASHTAG# in and hit the showerrrrrrrr #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to see the plurge tonight :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am i mentioned? I'm not black. "#USER#: Cool #USER# #USER# #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Taylor Swift." NOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! &gt;:|]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: There comes a point in your life when you realize who really matters, who never did, and who always will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Shit gets real after neck kisses."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fall asleep so I can blow your phone up babe ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't fucked up my hands or broken any knuckles in like a week or two. That's a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smokin mids? My nigga. Then don't pass that shit to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That strong my nigga then come match that shit with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one ain't for no FUCK NIGGAS. You a real nigga then fuck with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want my chest and back tatted.. like yesterday. 13 #HASHTAG# just isnt enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found all my 52 non followers thanks to #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Y'all new heat fans are not heat fans, y'all are LeBron James fans...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: When I was younger, $20 felt like $100. Now $20 feels like $1."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Lebron selling his newest shoe for $300? Look my dude YOU NOT JORDAN !"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Sometimes when #HASHTAG# pushes you away, they are really fighting for you to pull them closer. Don't let them go."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is a faggot. As well as all of his "#HASHTAG#" or whatever the fuck y'all call yourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free vip tickets to#HASHTAG#?!?!? MY LIFE IS COMPLETE#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is the place to be this year. So many dang stars walking around. Such a great environment. Only thing that sucks is $6 beers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: I really want to hear Obama say “nigga please” just once."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the cutting all this.blood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, if you have could keep me from ever waking up again that'd be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I still had my pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had the money to hire someone to kill me. I would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want it all to end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can never bring myself to make that final cut tho. Or to choke long enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad as it sounds I don't care. I'm tired of this life. Beyond tired. Better luck next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I had the balls to kill myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Using the term "starving" when their last meal was 4 hours ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Sometimes you just gotta whip out the D and see what happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Can't wait to see the purge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like how you get caught and yet aren't in the wrong for shit lmao. Fuck outta here. Real shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MF MIND FUCK "#USER#: Creepy American History. #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckong creepy "#USER#: Planetary alignment of Venus, Mercury and Saturn with Giza Pyramid. 3/12/12. #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: I may not be better than other people, but at least I'm different."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bitch is fucking money HUNGRY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out here at the #HASHTAG# country music festival in nashville ;) yee-haw #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: “#USER#: She's a bitch and you're an asshole. You're perfect for each other.” #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: “#USER#: She's a bitch and you're an asshole. You're perfect for each other.” #USER#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: I take a toke and all my worries go up in smoke."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many damn country singers in Nashville today, along with the stars of #HASHTAG# about to go meet some of em later today :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These three dogs are bacon OBSESSED and never leave me alone to cook lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# haha EVERRRRRYTHING is cheaper here ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3.28 in Nashville haha "#USER#: get your gas! it's 4.25 now!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: That awkward moment when you're actually telling the truth and someone still accuses you of lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: #HASHTAG# give their love completely but needs it back in return."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can safely assume I spend probably $100+ on lighters a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They need to create a lighter with GPS tracking in it. I would never lose a lighter again lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our perfect baby boy #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its sad how my life fits on these two suitcases.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>