<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Union didn’t sue when Democrats shutdown the government. Interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dems just want illegals, it equals votes for the dems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# More protestors should be whipped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Laura Loomer and Tommy Robinson are banned from Twitter, but this is allowed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is America. We speak and read English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You must have sat in the corner with the dunce hat on. No wonder socialists always fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Flake doesn’t know what the word conservative means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If they stop coming here illegally, this would not happen. Build the wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s what happens when a group of people refuse to accept and become a part of society in which they live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cry baby chuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shit another liberal activist that doesn’t understand science. The earth warms and cools in cycles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A liberal Nut case going to a liberal schoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No that was obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Seems like cry baby chuck won’t let America have what it wants, build the wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like trespassing and vandalism to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cry baby chuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cry baby chuck 👶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cry baby chuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cry baby chuck. Is this the best democrats have to offer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don’t let cry baby chuck push you around Mitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cry baby chuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your facts are wrong like usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Build the wall or shut the government down. Build the wall now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can’t handle the truth #USER#. Illegal immigration does make our country dirtier and poorer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Time to build the wall. We have laws which allow people to become citizens. Don’t come here illegally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love beef. Eat more beef America!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speak English. This is America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So can we say Muhammad always enjoyes sexual encounters with pigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Special council so desperate he turns to national enquirer. Laughable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She should have just got up and stood. Of coarse you cannot sit down and block a hallway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He does support the Muslim brotherhood. Facts are facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love bacon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Talk to geologist, they will tell you global warming is not man made. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# no wonder you loss the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Must be California, we don’t eat salad for a side in Montana even though we are in the salad region]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Leave them in prison they are criminals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What is there to judge, she is ugly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Fat ass monkey does not belong in school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The NRA has every right to call out groups that use science to conceal their political agenda. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wrong again #HASHTAG#. They mixed illegal votes with legal votes that’s called fraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Melania has way more class than that Michelle broad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let’s see mixing fraud ballots with legal ballots seems like evidence to me #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Our two nations are forever joined together by the spirit of revolution and the fight for freedom. 🇺🇸 🇫🇷]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Democrats are trying to steal the Florida election. Generating votes is called stealing an election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You do it everyday #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Grow up #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your wrong #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG# physically pushed her arm. We know #HASHTAG# is a wimp but to attack a girl is a new low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He physically pushed her arm away. #HASHTAG# probably could only win a fight with a girl intern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We got rid of Claire in Missouri, thank God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought liberals were supposedly better educated lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# poor loser. Man has been in government for so long he is in shock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought you were talking about your own journalist #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As usual media is fighting the people again #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is proof that lies become truth, #HASHTAG# cannot tell the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# misleads people. #HASHTAG# lies promoting their liberal agenda. #HASHTAG#sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Loved the costumes. About time we start education kids that illegals are not welcomed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#Opinion We have everything to fear. Our nation is based on law not mob rule #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They are illegals trying to invade our country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Looks like a threat to me stupid ass liberals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should fire if caravan is throwing stones. Stones can injury people #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nothing racist about the ad, it’s the truth #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And rules need to change when people start exploiting the rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is a gutless POS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# never cared about civility. He always vilified us that we’re against him, always calling us racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what, #HASHTAG# has the right to criticize fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Fake news again #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We should shoot at them. They are invading our country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s true. Trump exposed you guys and you cannot handle it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER#Opinion You fake news again #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# cannot even keep himself honest. All the lies he spreads on cnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I am proud to be a nationalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No way we believe an Univision reporter. They are anti American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your a joke. Liberals and your antifa started the violence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obviously this is a well planned out March. Soro’s and his crew are the only ones who could orchestrate this massive mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# is a loser. #HASHTAG# insults people all the time. Then cries when people make fun of him. Loser!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are a bunch of terrorist. They are a mob breaking the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Finally people taking a stand. We speak English in America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# CNN the comedy nutcase network]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Then break out the machine guns. Those illegals will understand that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Marriage is between a man and a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are trying to get free government handout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are looking for free government handout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# made up facts his whole presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Only in Oregon. Where the people are crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We don’t see the whole story. What caused the argument]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Call out the us military #HASHTAG#. Please we need to stop this mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I hope #HASHTAG# stops these illegals from coming to America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These are illegally coming to our country. We have laws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Grow a pair of balls #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If #HASHTAG# becomes governor expect him to send out violent mobs to stop decent people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because the press act like animals. You guys are so delusional with power. Look at #HASHTAG# he’s an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, got to love #HASHTAG#. Finally a president with the balls to take on the media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are illegal, they are not immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Close the border until they learn you cannot come to US illegally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You people need to grow up. The senator was joking. It was funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# About time we show #HASHTAG# our muscle. We cannot allow China to control the South China Sea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# has always been a POS senator. She finally got caught in one of her many lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a stupid story. She did not prove anything. She ran to liberal Stanford and not an independent researcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A liberal university #HASHTAG# did the research. She is no more Indian than John Smith lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Stanford professor performed the test. Liberal university and liberal senator. Probably is not reliable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It doesn’t matter if she was an adult. #HASHTAG# was president and she was an intern, that is definition of abuse of power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the US gymnastics team. They should be anti-Kaepernick, he is anti American crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# is our enemy, they slowly are trying to replace us as the world superpower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Antifa Thugs Furious After Police Release Their Pics — Let’s Make Them Famous! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only way to Dew with #HASHTAG# is to put them down hard. Hey #HASHTAG# come to Orlando, we ain’t your candyass Portland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Record inequality? Are you crazy minorities are getting everything they want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Melania Trump way better than Michelle Obama who always tried to preach to us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good time #HASHTAG# is fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Blimey. What is in the water in Rhode Island??? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey #HASHTAG# come down south. See how we will treat you morons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at these fucking idiot protestors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should not be blocking traffic. The driver was probably scared for their life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wonder what she sucked to get her job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully they arrested the wacko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My family were colonizers. We made America great, without us you wouldn’t have your freedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Easy she is a violent socialist. She wants to segment people, it’s what socialist do. No different than Germany in the 1930s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: .#USER# and #USER# are getting some insane reactions from protestors on Capitol Hill. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lagan only rules with liberals she has already divided the court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: 50-48 it's now JUSTICE Kavanaugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What you guys say is the evidence that there is a conspiracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The judge represents me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People need to grow up the helmet looked great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Time for Alaska to vote her out of office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Time for Alaska to vote her out. Obviously she not fit to be senator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s not a hero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If they are in America they should speak English]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What would you expect him to say he was one of the most liberal justices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# should be investigated for lying. She first hid them leaked #HASHTAG# letter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We don’t believe either of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sen Grassley recognizes lies. Only Democrats support lies, it’s over welcome justice Kavanaugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Say hello to Supreme Court Justice Kavanaugh. Finally a judge we can be proud of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Retweet this if Lindsey Graham became your favorite Senator over the past 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Kavanaugh Allegations Are Psychological Terrorism. It’s Time They End #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The turd durbin delaying again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Who would elect this wacko gal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It doesn’t take bravery to lie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# needs to tell the truth. Stop making up stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# standing up and fighting back. I love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Close the #HASHTAG# they have always been anti American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Low Birth Rates Parallel Not Just The Economy, But Also Feminism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many #HASHTAG# paid operatives are the news going to show harassing senators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We don’t believe you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s not cruel. They do not have the right to live here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Jeff Flake Isn’t A Truth-Seeker, He’s A Coward #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why people are innocent until evidence shows they are guilty. No evidence not guilty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# has resurfaced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# are violent people andrewgillum trying to cover up his true socialist feelings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh no the global warming idiots are coming back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Socialism at its best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# and her lawyer are con artist pure and simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There was no evidence against Kavanaugh #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She already thinks #HASHTAG# is guilty. Someone tell her there is no evidence that links him to sexual assault. Stupid foreigner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Think she’s a sweet old lady who simply wants justice for women? WRONG. THIS is the real Dianne Feinstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another feminazi on display]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# another delaying tactic by the Democrats and flake fell for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Flake he coward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# too bad sen booker doesn’t leave America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrats love to orchestrate everything they do. When did they meet to come up with this sideshow in the hallway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you and your Democrat friends treated #HASHTAG# belligerent and offensively. He had no choice but to stand up to you cowards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No evidence even her own friend as witness said it didn’t happen. That’s the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am so proud of #HASHTAG# today. He seen it was all political with no collaborating evidence #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: YES - there IS a point to this. And it does NOT look good for her. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Christine Blasey Ford is a heavy drinker also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# About time #HASHTAG# and we will support all yes votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I applaud #HASHTAG# for showing America how the Democrats have made this whole process political]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is twitter promoting this #HASHTAG# left wing bias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the turd 💩 Durban loses again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just got body slammed by #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is hammering the Democrats. He’s got the Democrats wheeling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Keep fighting we will #HASHTAG#. Great man for the Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Looks like a envelope full of cash lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She went to #HASHTAG# and was told to go to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# doesn’t even know if she paid for the polygraph test. Who doesn’t know if she paid for a $1000 test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yet another link between all these alleged accusations. This is why we don’t take their allegations seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#Opinion You guys in the media just cannot handle a president #HASHTAG# that makes you look stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This allegation is totally preposterous. They don’t even know the year it happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# coming out of the mouth of a socialist totally disconnected from reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like #HASHTAG# made it. Some more fake news remember #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# taking it to the media. This is a president all America should be proud of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She was in college. Did she go back to high school parties with guys 3 years younger than her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We don’t owe these women anything for lying. Sen Flake the dems puppet. Admit that they have no evidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Caught in lies again. Didn’t tell no one, now she has told many people. Doesn’t remember the year it happened or the house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All the French do is stick their tail between their legs and retreat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you cannot decide in a few hours, then you are as dumb as people say you are #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s about time we #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not worried at all. History proves when America stands alone and leads the world, the world becomes a safer place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am a NRA member and so glad to see #USER# and the #USER# in favor of #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well you will have to ban most of the Democrat party and their dehumanizing and abusive words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When your enemy laughs at you being the #HASHTAG# you know you have them scared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We don’t care about the #HASHTAG#, all the have done is take money from US to turn and around and try to block the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seems like she is lying. I’ve seen prof and scientist lie all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who cares what work she has done in the past. Doesn’t mean she is credible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I’m proud to support Kavanaugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As a #HASHTAG# member, I am proud to see them stand up for #HASHTAG#. Let’s work hard to get him confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Stand strong and tall against this smear campaign. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We must protect our farmers. Thank you for the support also #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like another liberal Democrat march lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No credible claims. Just vague memories after talking days with their liberal attorneys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh I see you stand behind your lying puppets #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>