<author lang="en" class="1">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The GOP is a dead party because for years they would not heed our warnings to purge every single Rino!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A little late, Ron. We knew this before the election!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course, it’s the Trump Vaccine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s a de facto union strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course he will. However, the media will report it was a success and his approval rating is going even higher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What did you think was going to happen when you failed to fight the Dems on election integrity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shut up and go away. You’re so tiresome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure we do. Valerie Jarrett.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She’s ready to step in if Joe goes down. That’s cuz she’s an expert on going down.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The legislature is gutless. They need to revoke his emergency powers!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If so, it’s long overdue!!! That Rino scum should’ve been ousted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually, the guy was a liberal. But facts don’t matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# About 75 million voters would like to see that happen. LoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unless the Rino leadership is totally ousted, and I mean completely, the GOP will never win back its base. Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have told you guys for months that Crooked Joe will not be president at the end of 2021. They will push him out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 1st Amendment is worthless without the Second Amendment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I miss #USER# Tweets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Who is EXCITED for President Trump’s #HASHTAG# speech tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The media doesn’t expect him to explain anything. The anti war crowd is silent. Go figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I'll be joining #USER# tonight from #USER# to talk about foreign policy. TUNE IN to #USER# at 9:00pm ET/8:00pm CT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Secret Service Sounds Alarm on Biden's Condition #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: President Trump is the leader of the Republican Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because he isn't afraid of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And what is the GOP as a whole going to do about it? Nuthin. Where's the leadership?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What happened to the "she must be believed" crowd?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not wise to answer that on here. Just sayin....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor old Joe will be out by the end of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's busy planning the next Romney family reunion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yup. No interest in them at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will watch Larry's show. He's a smart guy and has common sense. Blondie can go suck it. She'd rather be on CNN anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God Bless Rush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Gee....maybe they are actually the party of government employee unions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ask Paul Ryan. I'm sure he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: 'Donald J Trump' trends on Twitter for Presidents Day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That should do absolutely nothing.....WTF?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is exactly what the left does. They cannot accept losing, so they get more violent every time. Who is going to stop them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: President Trump: 2 Speaker Pelosi: 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Mitch McConnell hates Trump. We are all aware.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Impeachment House Manager Stacey Plaskett admits to the Senate that the election was stollen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Null and void.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How quickly they forget....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great points. I hope someone tells Pres Trump’s legal team. That guy didn’t seem too sharp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are all my notifications before yesterday erased? Big Social Media is at it again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Dictator Jobama is following orders. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Covid is designed to detain you within your homes and your borders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Watching the impeachment and all they do is read things other people wrote and tweeted trying to blame president Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: They are communist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: All I have to say is president Trump spoke the truth and he warned y’all. That’s all he could do. He did his part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You didn’t stand up for Pres Trump and election integrity. You caused this. So shut up and resign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Oh how will we ever survive? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Well done #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are too dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can he actually read?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Direct orders from Valerie Jarrett?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Half the state is homeless. The other half lives in Hollywood mansions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just like the Soviet Union.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because the GOP has utterly failed us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I’ve said this for years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That’s why he’s not a real leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Washington establishment is obsessed with Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We need term limits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You’d die with a mask on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have no idea the number of Trump voters that will never vote for them. Ever. The GOP is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hunter probably had to pick up a big envelope full of cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly as I predicted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Join your buddies in the Democrat Party, you Fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Barack Hussein Obama started that. I guess he thought it was “inclusive”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They don’t care about the Constitution or the law. They just don’t.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She’s too brave to fit in with the spineless GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just for the record, I want Biden to FAIL. FAIL in all respects. If he succeeds in his plans, America is GONE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crooked Joe promised us a long dark winter and that is exactly what we are going to get. Damn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antifa and BLM now officially have their "get out of jail free" card courtesy of the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They "won" and they can't enjoy it. They want more. they want blood. They're never f***ing satisfied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garth Brooks should be ashamed of himself. The dumb*ss should've sang, 'I've got friends in low places....." Disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This election was never about Biden. Ever. He’s a footnote at best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Being civil to them will get you nothing. They hate all of us and nothing will deter them from silencing us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It will hurt everyone except illegals and politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Glad I’m no longer a Republican. These idiots are a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# F***ing Democrats. That’s what they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump should have fired this loser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s why the GOP is a dead party. The Whigs will get more votes in 2022.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Figures. But the media will never report it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since they are all Dems (the FBI is making sure of that), I wonder if they even have guns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He will get to the bottom of nothing. He talks but does nothing. Ever. Screw you, Lindsey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Rove is just another Bushie globalist. He always hated Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mitch is a disgrace. Ditch Mitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why does anyone even listen to this cretin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They don’t realize that millions of us are already gone. The GOP is an empty shell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I wish this picture of Joe Biden holding hands with the leader of the KKK would go viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Duh. The GOP is the modern day Titanic and McConnell is Captain Smith. It’s all but sunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Check the Antifa membership list, you morons!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That’s kind of you, however, bailing out businesses that will never survive the lockdowns is a wasted effort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Turn the boats around or sink them and jail the illegal aliens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These traitors have the same future as the GOP does. Zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She doesn't represent the voters. She represents the majority of establishment hacks that still actually run the GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She has always been a vicious snake in a skirt. Anger fueled by a mixture of vodka and Prozac.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Vodka mixed with her Prozac probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Which means that the Muslim Brotherhood is actually pulling the strings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bye bye Fox. No one cares anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Roll Tide despite the bad refs and BS targeting calls!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What? You people have spent four years trying to overthrow my president!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeting? AYFKM? Total bullsh** College football refs suck. Roll Tide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve gotta say. Pelosi looks much better in a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sink the damn boats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well that pretty much eliminates 99% of the elected Republicans in Minnesota.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How can anyone defeat them when they control all of the voting machines??????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Gotta admit that I feel the same. Never this say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s an all out assault on conservatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Romney’s puppet and spy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From this day on, all GOP fundraising letters that I get will be marked “Return to Sender” with a big bold Sharpie!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The GOP cowards will be getting all their fundraising requests back in mail marked “Return to Sender”!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Deep State bullsh**]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because you’re afraid of the media....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which was Ryan and McConnell’s project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Be safe. I will always stand with Pres Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, the fact that there is even a question about what Mike Pence will do today speaks volumes about the backbone of Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why should there even be a question of whether Pence will come through?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is GOP's last chance to survive as a political party. If they fail today, they can just close the doors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are they going to allow you time to do it? Do you guys have all the evidence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd say that is on the money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably never. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They won’t be done counting for 48 hours. No one will be in the senate from Georgia tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like about time for a pipe to bust so they can stop counting until the trucks come with more fake Dem ballots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The guy never heard of a disguise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why should we be surprised? They got away with it two months ago. Why would they stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly, Ann has lost her marbles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Swine. The swamp is in every state and not just in DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And those two just slinked away quietly. How much were they paid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The GOP in Georgia had two months to prevent fraud and they chose to do nothing. Fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, Captain Ramius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Correct. But we will never get term limits except by a convention of the states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I told you guys. What do you expect? The Georgia GOP did nothing since November to prevent the fraud from being repeated! Fools!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not as hard as keeping her away from a buffet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And we need their votes counted correctly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fox News has its puppets like Brian K urging Trump to concede because "there is no evidence" of vote fraud. Unbelievable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Demolish it and make a parking lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what ever happened to the legislature revoking his “emergency” tyranny powers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now we will see if there are any honest judges.....good luck with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe Trump wants them to hear and see for themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If only he'd fired those jackasses a year ago. Maybe things would be different....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is he afraid that she will sit on him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Purge the RINOs! If the GOP is not a conservative party, it is a USELESS party!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Turn Nadler and Stacy Abrams loose and they could demolish the biggest buffet on earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why the hell is anyone talking about who is running in 2024?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He sure did. That guy changed into an establishment hack when we ran with Romney in 2012.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What do you have to hide? Or you just scared of the establishment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pretty much says it. They are "comfortable losers."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I presume that you and your fellow GOP members are NOT going to comply. Right???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who? I thought Mpls abolished the PD???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the weak GOP, led by Doubt, will go right along with it....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Despite the fact that Crazy Bernie got screwed again in the Democrat primaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me or does Stacy Abrams look like she swallowed Oprah?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Jihad Squad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did Ocrazyo-Cortez have some plastic surgery on her body? Just axing....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s actually a bigger fraud than Obama convincing people that he was an American citizen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# First, you’re a nobody. Second, you’re a Democrat. Run in the correct party, you A-hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That guy was a jackoff in 2016 and he still is. Pay him no attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I pray that is true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 17% more than Obama and 24% more than Crooked Hillary? No f***ing way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the end, the Dems stick together and we always have Rino traitors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But you can’t sell it because nobody wants to live in sh**hole NY. Too bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden hasn’t been elected!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You’re not a Republican!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stand up for our president!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whiners. They think we are stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s been that way for years. People are just seeing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They’re in on it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes! I see another national championship!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How about we don’t spend the tax money at all???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I told you people that McConnell should’ve been replaced!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They won’t work? Fire them all!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Teachers should not be allowed to strike. Overpaid, under worked union thugs is what they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don’t forget that many citizens will get nothing due to the income limits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel sorry for people who don’t drink. When they get up in the morning, that’s as good as they feel all day....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because they cannot buy him or control him. That’s why the establishment hates our president!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We will see on Jan. 6....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should tell the left to f*** off and keep campaigning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Charles, he works for the establishment and the Dems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lots of people will not get it due to the income limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And this ex-Deep state hack is qualified to attack a senator why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She wants to get poked on national tv? Exhibitionist....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don’t give advice to someone that is 1,000 times the man you are. Just shut up and go away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No! Test people that are sick. Stop testing healthy people just so that you can claim more “cases” and shut things down!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or is the testing that has produced more “cases” than ever just plain faulty??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He has always been a full RINO. The rest was just an act. Just like Lindsey's act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big Social Media hates it when they cannot control us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been telling you guys this for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not enough if these cowardly so-called conservative judges will not step up and restore the integrity of our elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He takes his orders from the DC establishment. It's that simple. That squirrel should've been replaced by Trump on Day One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She appears to be headed to another buffet at Golden Corral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's not a failure. He has been doing exactly what the establishment has told him to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are essential to the Democrat Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is working for the establishment. Always has been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I said that in 2014. I still regret those two votes. Damn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dumbed down losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What the Founding Fathers would DO is important. They wouldn’t just talk about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They’re just waiting for the next email from Soros with new instructions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But there is no gang problem....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s a disgrace. Whatever happened to the good old USA?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>